Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Hmm… Good morning, everyone.
Krish NAik: Just check the chats are opened or not.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think Chatindar has already dived.
Krish NAik: So I think it's good.
Krish NAik: So, Lakshmi, today, the continuation of the project, okay, as I can see, Chatvindar, all that you did, and the changes I was going to say.
Krish NAik: So that H5 doesn't mess up with AWS already, according to your system, you have done the setup for that.
Krish NAik: Yes, actually, like, Jatin, initially, I used that serverless for the Lambda function name. Okay, previous to that, I didn't use that, as I was testing it within another user account for that test, but fine, you have already done that. JQ installation, you have done using Choco, great.
Krish NAik: Linux and Mac directly can be done. Alright.
Krish NAik: Today it will be to the continuation of,
Krish NAik: the same project, because next week, another project that will be starting. I think before that project, a little bit, we'll be talking with respect to CRAG and SRAG, okay? Because till now, I'm not done the implementation, this week only I will be doing that.
Krish NAik: And then finally.
Krish NAik: I think, next week we can start Project 3. Okay, so two core components of RAC.
Krish NAik: CRAG, and I think that part will be new for you guys. REST, hybrid RAG, the re-ranking, those things will be implemented.
Krish NAik: Alright, as far as Sultan, I was telling you, I was not able to get the output for step 3, build the upper image for no output. Yes, it won't be having any output as well. That is only the Docker build that I told you.
Krish NAik: Tier this installation. Alright, fine. You can create a guest, Jatander, a public guest, okay, and you can share that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… Directly, it will be easier for… Okay.
Krish NAik: Alright, so generally, not the complete project is built.
Krish NAik: By a single-person SK, so according to your role in that particular project, you have to mention that. Resumes till now, like, even I don't have. Probably I have to look for exact, resumes, okay? So, little bit that, build up according to some product-based organizations that I'll be sharing them.
Krish NAik: Alright, so I think we are good to go with our continuation.
Krish NAik: So today, we will try to complete the deployment.
Krish NAik: So, let me start sharing my screen.
Krish NAik: In my system, a lot of variables have changed, so this is the top three, I think. I'll wait.
Krish NAik: Alright, those metrics.
Krish NAik: That will be much more in the form of the eval metrics.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Alright, Sunny has few of them, but again, those are much more from service-based point of view.
Krish NAik: Those are not product-based organizations, that's…
Krish NAik: All right, so I think, we are good to go. In the last class, okay, till what point you guys have done, I think,
Krish NAik: creating the lambda function, because still, this is the main step that you need to follow. After that, like, the rest of the steps through a single execution, it is possible.
Krish NAik: Alright, I think yesterday you guys have created the ECR.
Krish NAik: Yes or no? Good.
Krish NAik: Okay, in local builder success, fine, local builder's not right now not required, because it was for the Lambda environment that we did.
Krish NAik: So, I think, with respect to…
Krish NAik: the first part. I'm just waiting. When I will…
Krish NAik: have a look that till which point. S3 bucket you guys have created?
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: then I think from this point, we can do the continuation. Yes? I think after the ECR part.
Krish NAik: Perfect.
Krish NAik: Now, the image that you have built, you can, push
Krish NAik: that particular image, or through our CICD pipeline that I have in deploy.yml, through that also, we can do the push to that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so the push part is fine. Before pushing, just be sure, because again, I don't want you to do the build. It will be better that, if you will be, directly working with the Lambda function.
Krish NAik: Okay, so let's start working on the lambda. I think today we can start creating the lambda, and then similarly, we will be creating the function URL with respect to lambda.
Krish NAik: Could not have some error, but tried to push.
Krish NAik: Before the push, you need to do a login. I think,
Krish NAik: somewhere with respect to this. If you have done, then only you will be able to push to that particular
Krish NAik: Ethiopt.
Krish NAik: Alright, so first of all, let's start with the first part, okay? So I think… This is…
Krish NAik: Alright…
Krish NAik: Just to eat.
Krish NAik: I think it'll be better if I switch to
Krish NAik: Let me check, the repos, if you guys have already created that.
Krish NAik: repository mean.
Krish NAik: I think this terminal would be so much helpful to me.
Krish NAik: Fine. So, yesterday, what is the name of the report? So, whatever the name of the report that you have given, okay? So, I think we can do an AWS ECR.
Krish NAik: describe, just have a check on that. Okay, so in my case, I think the name of the report that I created, it was Doc. So, you can get a confirmation according to the name that you have given.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I think, rows should have one element instead of 3.
Krish NAik: Just filter.
Krish NAik: Alright, yes, I got it.
Krish NAik: The major ones in the form of All right.
Krish NAik: I have multiple, images here inside this Text2SQL, so let me just get a verification.
Krish NAik: Let me just delete. You guys don't need to do anything. Okay, so in my ECR, let me check, and I will delete the old images for you.
Krish NAik: I think… step to SQL, okay?
Krish NAik: Sweet.
Krish NAik: Alright, I have cleaned now, so the image that you have built.
Krish NAik: Because of timeout, okay, I will look into that, because right now, even, I cannot say exactly what can be your issue, Santosh.
Krish NAik: Alright, so right now, for me also, this is pretty much blank, okay? Now, I will go to the deploy.yml, because there are a few hard-coded things that I have kept.
Krish NAik: So, inside my GitHub workflows, deploy.yml, okay? Okay, so just be sure, inside this deploy.yml file, you keep your ECR repository name. Okay, so for example, in my case.
Krish NAik: It is RAG, text-to-SQL doc that I have kept it.
Krish NAik: Okay? So, the same name, yesterday that you have created, pass that. And similarly, for example, the lambda function that I have, okay, before that, I have given the name. So, this is the name of the lambda function. You can keep the same name, or just change the variable. So, during the lambda function creation, you can change that.
Krish NAik: So, I'll be changing the names.
Krish NAik: A little bit, so that, everything starts from fresh, okay? So, let me just give the name server here.
Krish NAik: An ECR repo, it's clean right now, so I think I can use the same repo.
Krish NAik: Other than that, because these things are not available in your secrets, if you have checked the secret yesterday that you have filled up, so it only be available there. So right now, I'll be creating this lambda function. The ECR is already available to me, okay?
Krish NAik: So, just be sure line number, 9 and 10, you're putting the correct values, and similarly, I hope the region is east-east 1 for everyone, okay? So, please do this change in line number 9 and 10. Put your ECR repo, so whatever the name that you have given yesterday, that's another change is the lambda function name that I will be creating right now, okay?
Krish NAik: So I won't be using that serverless, I'll be using server only for…
Krish NAik: Alright, so one change that I have done here…
Krish NAik: Okay, now let's get back and start, creating our Lambda function.
Krish NAik: I think I don't need this anymore.
Krish NAik: Where is my traya, trayathara?
Krish NAik: Okay, ECR login registry, total, and the function update.
Krish NAik: Hold it.
Krish NAik: Okay, so step 4.4 is the main one. Okay, so from here, I will just copy this command.
Krish NAik: Okay, and in this command, you can see in the second line, it's written serverless, so this time, I'll be creating, like, I will remove the less in my case. So if you are using serverless, it's fine. There won't be any type of changes there.
Krish NAik: Let me just copy this.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now, I can create it from the UI also, but, I'm creating it directly from the CLI. So, in the Lambda creation function, I'm telling, first of all, what will be the function name, then the package type, it can… right now, I'll be using an ECR image, so that's why that ECR…
Krish NAik: Like, what type, so it will be a Docker image, so for that, I've defined here image, then comes…
Krish NAik: code image URI from where the, it will be picked up. Okay, so here you have to update that particular ECR URI that you have used, okay? So, according to your URI, so my URI is…
Krish NAik: From here, I can get the URI. Let me just go here.
Krish NAik: Or, you can get it from your terminal also, okay? So, that is also fine, so… but quickly, I think I can copy this one, okay? So, the second one is the URL. So, this URI that I am using right now.
Krish NAik: So I will paste the URI here.
Krish NAik: And if you want to use variables, that's fine, you can simply do the export of easier.
Krish NAik: Okay, my AWS account ID, again, this one is new, so let me update this variable also.
Krish NAik: the Lambda function will pick up the image from the E here, and then it will deploy it correct.
Krish NAik: to AWS account ID, let me get the account ID.
Krish NAik: Alright, so here, I've pulled from here, the ECR that will be picked up. This is fine, rule, I have passed.
Krish NAik: Then, architecture, so here, I'm working with X8664 architecture. Previously, as I told, like, the other alternative is ERM64. Timeout for this lambda function, I've given 900 seconds.
Krish NAik: Memory size?
Krish NAik: 3000MB. FRL storage, I've given 10GB right now. This is the description for the lambda function, and in which region I want to create this particular lambda. So these are the main parameters.
Krish NAik: Alright, so let me start creating this.
Krish NAik: Does not exist, write text to SQL, just let me check, when calling the function URL.
Krish NAik: Lambda create function… why it's telling it does not exist? Just delete.
Krish NAik: Create function, image source… I think I have passed the correct ECR URL.
Krish NAik: Just tweet, because… Yes, this is the correct ECR URI that I have here.
Krish NAik: Just tweet.
Krish NAik: TechSooth SQL API, image name, the complete image.
Krish NAik: Okay, this is not the repo URI, so this is actually the
Krish NAik: image URI. Alright, fine, fine, fine, fine. One simple change, because right now, as this is the repo URI, okay, within the image, right now, as I've deleted all the image, so it looks like I have to push the image.
Krish NAik: Fine Fine, fine, fine, woo.
Krish NAik: Actually, then again, I need to do the build, because yesterday, I have deleted, I think, yes, I don't have the image.
Krish NAik: I should not have deleted that. You need the image URI, actually.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine, one thing that I can do here, just wait.
Krish NAik: Mmm…
Krish NAik: Let me just, do a new push. I think the new push will be taken care by that, so…
Krish NAik: Automatically, the image will be building, okay? So, just wait.
Krish NAik: Let me just close this file, deploy.yml. Again, I will change back to serverless for now.
Krish NAik: Yeah, I'm good.
Krish NAik: Mmm… niche out of lunch?
Krish NAik: So, let me just make a random change and deploy.ympt.
Krish NAik: Alright, just wait, let me just, move the screen once.
Krish NAik: Well, they deployment for…
Krish NAik: Just wait, okay, so…
Krish NAik: Because I don't want to build the image again in my local, it's better to do it in the pipeline. So…
Krish NAik: Let me see, whether the deployment has started or not.
Krish NAik: Well, I feel… this should be there.
Krish NAik: Because… This one, alright.
Krish NAik: Okay, it worked, actually.
Krish NAik: Because I don't know, probably some type of spaces might create the issue, okay? So, when I tested the command, I think the new
Krish NAik: lambda function has been created, okay? So, I can do a verification from… Here, tellability, A, lambda.
Krish NAik: Okay, so as you can see, rack text to SQL Server, okay? So, this is fine. Later on, I will change it into deploy.yml, and the rest of the deployment will be done. Now, whenever you are building any Lambda functions, as in all Lambda functions, we have a lot of variables.
Krish NAik: those environment variables, we need to pass it, okay? So, once the function is created, in the next step, we need to update that particular function with respect to the environment variables, okay? So, I think I have given that particular
Krish NAik: Update command.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, guys, please have it checked, okay, if you want, because,
Krish NAik: I think, after removing some blank spaces, that particular command work, okay? So, do you want me to share this particular command in Notion? Please let me know.
Krish NAik: If you want it… because it's the same command only, I think because of one blank space, the issue was there.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I think, this is the project too. Okay, so here only, below, I'll be creating a board block.
Krish NAik: Whoops.
Krish NAik: Thanks for now.
Krish NAik: Okay, so the entire command, my command that I have given. And just be sure, here I have, in the name, it's server.
Krish NAik: Okay, so if you are using server or serverless, just maintain that across, every command, whenever you are working with that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so Santosh is telling an error occurred. What is the error, Santosh? Invalid parameter when calling the create function.
Krish NAik: The image manifest config, or the layer, okay? And don't use my ECR URI. See, again, this is, ECR URI that I have passed. It's mine. Okay, please try to use your own. Okay, don't directly, blindly copy-paste, just be sure you are updating that particular variable.
Krish NAik: Okay? So, just be sure about that.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: If this part is done, then in the next step.
Krish NAik: Okay, so below, also, in one shot, I will provide it. It will be easier to look into this one, yes.
Krish NAik: Image will leave that part, Matesh. If image will leave that part locally, okay, so whoever, it's not necessary to build the image, it's better to do it in our CI-CD pipeline directly.
Krish NAik: Now, once my lambda… I think for everybody the Lambda function got created, please provide a confirmation, based on, the parameters that I have provided. And just be sure you are providing your own function name. So, in my case, like, I have given you without this
Krish NAik: only that server, there is no list, and please use your own image ECR URI, okay? And then provide me a confirmation that, yes, it is working, because I think if it is working in my system, it should work in your system also.
Krish NAik: Rajat, right now, locally, you don't need to do that, okay? Whoever is trying to do the build, it's not necessary. This is a Docker Lambda build, okay? So it's not necessary for your local.
Krish NAik: So, first of all, just try to create the…
Krish NAik: Lambda function, and then let me know in the chat that, yes, it is working. Because once the function is done, then in the next step, like, we'll be updating that particular function.
Krish NAik: It takes around 1-2 minutes.
Krish NAik: Let me just paste this command once. Lambda function wait active.
Krish NAik: And in my case, I've given the name, Server.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I know the function has been created, there is no issue with the function.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please have a check.
Krish NAik: Everybody. First of all, just create a Lambda function. You don't need to do any Docker builds in your local.
Krish NAik: Because the local docker image is different, and the one that I'll be pushing in LambdaDAT will be different.
Krish NAik: Yeah, so
Krish NAik: Alright, so these are my main,
Krish NAik: what Docker image… there is no Docker image name required, whoever is telling, like, San and others. See, when I executed this command in this, there are no Docker image parameters, there's only the ECR URI that needs to be passed.
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no. See, I… this is my ECR URL, this is not, like, specific to an image.
Krish NAik: Okay?
Krish NAik: Because I think in my… I have done the push, actually, because of that, I feel that if that image is available… let me just check… Elastic Container Registry…
Krish NAik: your image UI will be different, mine will be different.
Krish NAik: Because, yes, this image is around 5GB that I do have.
Krish NAik: Okay, 1224, write text to SQL,
Krish NAik: What are the valid source image.
Krish NAik: the image URL is different, we do not have the image, okay? That's why I did the deployment. If you don't have the image, then actually, if you have built the image, then you need to push the image.
Krish NAik: Okay, so that is the, finest tip, because here, actually, see, I have done the tagging of this image with AMD64. So, because of this particular tag, that image is getting picked.
Krish NAik: Okay, because I was planning to do it directly, there.
Krish NAik: You can, leave the Lambda part then. Okay, without the Lambda part, if you try to deploy.
Krish NAik: Okay. No, no.
Krish NAik: One thing is, you can do the local build, and then push the image, okay? But again, for that, I have to do it manually. Let me do the build again, it will take some time, then let me go in that particular direction, okay? Just wait, if you guys are getting there, just wait, I'll push the image, and then you will do that. Okay, so let me do that, first of all.
Krish NAik: Alright, so platform, this is the command to build the local docker. Okay, so just wait. Once this is built, then I will, tag it, and then I will push it.
Krish NAik: Okay, sorry, ECR URI, I need to pass it again here.
Krish NAik: Just wait.
Krish NAik: Well, this is the other alternative. I was planning that directly the build will take place.
Krish NAik: Where is my… Not here, thank you.
Krish NAik: Okay, then let's wait for the image build. Just wait step-by-step only. I was planning not to do that, because this build will again take, some time for me.
Krish NAik: Just wait, I think you don't have that particular tagged version, that's why you were getting there, just wait.
Krish NAik: locally do the build, and then we will do the push, okay? So, others also just be sure in your local machine.
Krish NAik: Because for me, it's already available in my CI-CD pipeline, so it worked for me. I think in your case, it's not working because of that.
Krish NAik: So, just wait. I am doing the build, then I will manually push it, okay, and then, manually I will do the selection.
Krish NAik: Alright, people, don't paste the error right now as I'm building locally the image, and then I'll be pushing it. So, you can also follow the same steps.
Krish NAik: Yes, this will take more time.
Krish NAik: Actually, you can, do the CICD push also. If you have, all the variables, then what will happen? See?
Krish NAik: Again, I will say it's not necessary to do the local bid. If you are doing a push here, automatically till this step, so when I'm telling, so just wait.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, yes.
Krish NAik: Okay, till this step, it will go. And then, updating the lambda function, here, actually, it will fail. So if you try to do a new push, you will see that automatically these things have started.
Krish NAik: Okay, so, like, it will be directly available, so you don't need to do a local build if you feel, because this deployment will fail at this particular point of time.
Krish NAik: So that is the another alternate way. In whichever way you want to do it, it's fine.
Krish NAik: Local build is done, great, just wait once my local build is done.
Krish NAik: Okay, in my case, also, I think the local build is done, okay? Now, to push the image, you need to do, first of all, the verification, you need to do an ECR login. So, for that, I think already I've given you the command. You can just take that command, and you can paste it. So, I think my ECR URI don't need this part. Yes, this is the one.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you can copy this.
Krish NAik: Let me just, paste it here, and here the ECR URI, I will just update it to my URL.
Krish NAik: Which is, this one, rag text to SQL doc.
Krish NAik: Okay, it will say login succeed. I think that, login succeed will come.
Krish NAik: Okay, as you can see, login is succeed. Now, in the next step, first, I have to tag the image, and then I have to push the image.
Krish NAik: Okay, so for that also, I think I provided the command for doing the tag.
Krish NAik: So, this is my Docker one. Only the first one that you need, the second one, really, you don't need.
Krish NAik: Okay, so the first one which I have here, let me update the URI variables.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think this is the part where I'm tagging the image that I have locally built. As you can see, the latest tag, that tag I am changing to AMD64. Okay, now the tagging is done. Now, in the next step, I have to push the image, so that's why that docker push command is coming.
Krish NAik: Okay? So, so the second one is not required right now. Okay, so directly you can push it.
Krish NAik: So, one command is for the latest one to be pushed, and the other one is for the AMD64. Right now, I'm focused on the AMD64.
Krish NAik: Okay, AMD64, I think this is the push.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now, as you can see, the push has started. So everybody… see, manually I have done it.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you guys can do the verification manually.
Krish NAik: still waiting for the build already, I know, because in my system, a lot of things were captured, and yesterday, I showed you, like, in my system, it took around, 700 to 800 seconds.
Krish NAik: When you are actually working with ARM64, the build is much more faster, but just because of PyTorch was creating the issue, I shifted it to x64 architecture.
Krish NAik: So in this way, please try to push the image, okay, and then you try to create the Lambda function.
Krish NAik: So, two… both the things I have shown you, like, in whichever way, you can do it with a push of CICD also, directly in GitHub, it will be created in…
Krish NAik: the CICD pipeline, okay, and then it will be pushed. That will be done automatically, so I think that process is much easier, rather than doing a local bid.
Krish NAik: What is ECR URI? You can get the ECR URI from here, whenever you are creating any ECR repo, so this is the ECR URI.
Krish NAik: Whoever is asking, I think Balaji.
Krish NAik: Yes, it is, correct. In AWS ECR Describe repositories, that will also show what are the repositories that you have in total. Okay. So, let me just show you that particular command also. So here, if I paste it…
Krish NAik: Describe the tools.
Krish NAik: So all the repositories that I have, all will be shown in one place.
Krish NAik: So right now, I think I am working with, text-to-SQL doc.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: I think Text2SQL, 123 I have, Rack Text2SQL, That one I have, so…
Krish NAik: Sam, this is a CB deploy, I think this is the other one.
Krish NAik: Okay, and this is where my Text2SQL doc… this is the one that I'm currently using.
Krish NAik: Okay, the last one that I…
Krish NAik: So, this is a manual push.
Krish NAik: So, in whichever way you want to do it, please do it.
Krish NAik: Because if you initiate your CI-CD pipeline, how many have initiated the CICD pipeline? Please tell me.
Krish NAik: how many of you have initiated the CICD pipeline? Just try to do a push, because at least you will see that, yes, rather than doing a local push, this is much easier. Even I did it in the first step, no? Because I know, in your case, you have the AWS credentials set, yes, that you guys have done it.
Krish NAik: Okay, and right now, the main,
Krish NAik: till this point, you don't need any environment variables, okay? Later on, for the lambda function, it is actually required. So at least till this step, it will go, and then it will fail. That is fine. But you will see that the build of the image and the tagging, pushing, everything will take place automatically.
Krish NAik: Okay, yes, it will start, it's not stuck. Rajat is getting processed, it means that. Okay, initiated the CICDC, everybody, please initiate the CICD. If you want me, I can create a new ECR, and I can show you that part.
Krish NAik: Do you want me to do that?
Krish NAik: let me know. If you want, then I will wait 2 to 3 minutes, the task that you are doing, because I know, locally the image that I have built, it will be also pushed. Otherwise, the other way. I will just clean the repo, and then again, I will do it, okay? Just, for a confirmation.
Krish NAik: Because I know in both of you, it should be done.
Krish NAik: Okay, so in the meantime, just let me, create a new, private, rather than let me use the command style. I think it will be much easier.
Krish NAik: Alright, so this is the one.
Krish NAik: Okay, here I'm… I will give the name SQL, after that, I will add the term server for now.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I'm just creating a fresh one.
Krish NAik: Alright, this got created, rack TextualSQL Server.
Krish NAik: Now, in my deploy.yml file, whereas, just with my deploy. Deploy.yml file, I will update this name.
Krish NAik: Okay, so previously, this name that I have used, sql-doc, this time I will be updating to this name.
Krish NAik: Okay, and…
Krish NAik: ECR update.
Krish NAik: Any time limit on CICT, the first build will take time. And then, actually, I'm saving all the catches, so that the next time you push, it will be much faster. Initially, it took around 15 to 20 minutes.
Krish NAik: See, that's why I actually started with ARM64. ARM64 build was much faster. It was close to 8 minutes to 10 minutes. Okay, but X64, like, first it took 30 minutes for the entire build to be taken, but after that.
Krish NAik: Using UV and a few other optimizations somehow reduce close to 18 minutes. Okay, so the first time the build will take place.
Krish NAik: Okay, so here I'm updating, see, let me update the change, ECR update.
Krish NAik: Rishi, why… see, Rishi, if you have posted the image, then I think… write text to SQL…
Krish NAik: It's not supported.
Krish NAik: When calling the function…
Krish NAik: is not supported, because… not supported. Okay, alright, let me check manually, and then I will do it.
Krish NAik: Then, in my case, how it picked up, that's why.
Krish NAik: How many of you are getting that, not supported, not supported? Alright, fine.
Krish NAik: Let me, first of all do this, check this one.
Krish NAik: Because I feel this is a much safer one to do it, rather than doing a local well completely.
Krish NAik: Okay? So this time I picked up,
Krish NAik: The ECR1, ECR already, right?
Krish NAik: GH…
Krish NAik: I don't have any ECI URI here, then it is fine.
Krish NAik: Okay, now let's get back to our deployment page.
Krish NAik: Where is the deployment? Yes.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now… Because in my cage, the catch is done. So… okay, now, can you see here?
Krish NAik: verify the ECR login and build and task. Now, this place, it will take time. So, just wait.
Krish NAik: Because a lot of installations are there.
Krish NAik: Alright, even you got the same error. Alright, then I will try to… because I think for everybody, the push is working, yes, on…
Krish NAik: Otherwise, see, manually, I can create the lambda function from UI also.
Krish NAik: That is much easier for me.
Krish NAik: But, I thought about using the CLL. Okay, if that is not working, again, I will test it by creating a new function.
Krish NAik: for judgment.
Krish NAik: Because right now, in my case also, the image is getting built, and then it will be pushed.
Krish NAik: So, once this, I have till this step is done.
Krish NAik: Okay, then I will move to the next one. So, post, build tag, push image.
Krish NAik: That's lane.
Krish NAik: Okay, just wait, because if it is not working, let me check this part.
Krish NAik: Because create lambda function, so this is the command that I have given.
Krish NAik: Okay, so in this command, the same command if you are telling that, The rat?
Krish NAik: just check the, tag, I think the tag is with respect to…
Krish NAik: the latest one, just with. I have created the new one.
Krish NAik: This is the new server one.
Krish NAik: And inside that right now, the image is not pushed.
Krish NAik: Text to SQL… okay, this is the latest one that got pushed, initially.
Krish NAik: All right. Fine.
Krish NAik: Now, whenever, whoever is using that AMD64, okay, change that tag.
Krish NAik: to latest for now. Okay, just change the tag to lettuce. Other than that, don't do anything. People who are getting not supported. For them, I'm telling you. Change the AMD64 tag to latest.
Krish NAik: Please change the tag, guys.
Krish NAik: And then tell me whether it's working or not.
Krish NAik: It is not necessary to create the Lambda function before the CICD. If you have not created the Lambda function, simply you will get an error here.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now, can you see here, exporting the image?
Krish NAik: Okay, so if I say about exporting the image.
Krish NAik: Tune the image will be available inside my report. So, really, a local build is not required. Everything will be done in runtime.
Krish NAik: So, this is the name, okay, and soon the image will be available, so once I get the confirmation.
Krish NAik: So, that's why I'm telling you, local build is not necessary. Through CI-CD, do it, it's much better. At least things will be captured, and again, if you try to redeploy, things will be picked up from catchers. So, within, 4 minutes, the deployment will be done.
Krish NAik: Alright, I will just look into that, because in this step, if it's working for me.
Krish NAik: Just be sure you have all the permissions of S3 and others, the things that we have done in the last class.
Krish NAik: Because this particular command is exactly the same that I have provided, there is no difference here.
Krish NAik: Lettest one…
Krish NAik: Because, again, if I try to change the function name, and if I try to create something new.
Krish NAik: Yeah, so George tweet.
Krish NAik: Yes, for me, this is getting created, so…
Krish NAik: Alright, let me just check the hashings.
Krish NAik: Exporting the layers will take time. The image is picked, that's fine.
Krish NAik: Even for me, you can see.
Krish NAik: It, okay, so… Right now, I think the container image digest has been provided.
Krish NAik: And this is around 7376 already, and this is the report text result. So, I can see that if I reload this page, I'll be getting the image.
Krish NAik: Okay, so yes, the image is available. Because right now, as you can see in the image, both the image stacks, latest as well as AMD64, so I thought about, picking up any one, either AMD64 or the latest stack.
Krish NAik: Okay, because…
Krish NAik: Right now, this was the main purpose, rather than doing a local build, just check that through CICT directly, it will be available in the report.
Krish NAik: Okay, now I will change the…
Krish NAik: repository. I think that will be better in the first case.
Krish NAik: Okay, so repository… Aww.
Krish NAik: let me, get my ECR report according to the main document that I have, so just…
Krish NAik: That's why I'm just creating each component, so that it becomes much easier for you, so that you can quickly get it.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I think I can just take this particular command.
Krish NAik: Okay, and so, text to SQL, I think after that I have added the term server.
Krish NAik: Okay, Text2SQL, server. Just wait, where I've given text to SQL Server, yes, this is the name.
Krish NAik: Alright, this is the output text. From here, I'll be getting the ECR URI. As you can see, this is the same one.
Krish NAik: Okay, so this I have copied. Now,
Krish NAik: based on the new function, okay, let's create a new function only.
Krish NAik: Again, I will create so many functions, alright.
Krish NAik: Alright, so here, only this part that needs to be changed.
Krish NAik: Okay, and I'm giving a name, server… Test.
Krish NAik: Again, a new function that I'm creating, package, code, image, URI,
Krish NAik: server role, everything that I have pasted it here. Execution rule is available, architecture, timeout, memory size, okay? So let me just see whether I'm getting any error or not.
Krish NAik: Okay, I can see that, again, the new Lambda function got created.
Krish NAik: So guys, please have it checked.
Krish NAik: Because I feel that it will work.
Krish NAik: For how many of… it's working, because manually, see, so many lambda functions I created.
Krish NAik: So, please let me know.
Krish NAik: And just be sure, like, you have all the permissions and others.
Krish NAik: If you… I think, with respect to my…
Krish NAik: Okay, this is the Lambda Trust, policy.
Krish NAik: If you have to get this… this access is much more from the other side, so I think it should work.
Krish NAik: If it's not working, then I have to check, that part.
Krish NAik: Okay, username with my main one, fine.
Krish NAik: For anybody that's working.
Krish NAik: Please let me know in the chat. For anybody. If it is not working, it's fine, don't say it in the chat. For how many operators working?
Krish NAik: Docker pushes in progress, alright. The push is in progress fine.
Krish NAik: Because, if you want me to change the function name, I can do that.
Krish NAik: Okay, and then again, I can start with the redeployment.
Krish NAik: Viraj, okay, you were telling me, should I create the… okay, already told. Getting error in the CI-CD pipeline. CICD pipeline, you will get an error, because you have not created the Lambda function yet.
Krish NAik: But are you getting, in this stage, build, tag, push, image to easier? In this stage, are you getting any errors?
Krish NAik: Tell me that.
Krish NAik: Because here you will see that all images pushed to ECR successfully.
Krish NAik: Now, this part is fine, updating the Lambda function. If you don't have the Lambda function only, what it will update. I hope you get my point.
Krish NAik: Where you are getting the error in the build, people who are telling.
Krish NAik: That's where I get this error. Where barology? In this update lambda function part?
Krish NAik: Quickly tell me. Because I need that confirmation, because I think that you guys can see this thing in your screen. Otherwise, I will ask someone to share your screen.
Krish NAik: That's the main thing, because otherwise, even I cannot understand better.
Krish NAik: No in-build tag, my Docker image got pushed.
Krish NAik: Exporting layers.
Krish NAik: Alright, so this is where you got the error with respect to exporting the layers, because, exporting the layers. Alright, it's better, so one of you just, raise your hand, share your screen. Because in my case, if it's working, it should work in your case also.
Krish NAik: So, let's take Balaji and Rajat, okay? So, others.
Krish NAik: only two people I will look. So, first of all, Balaji, you can start, sharing your screen and tell me.
Krish NAik: In the CITB part, we were exactly the resulted.
Balaji Rengan: It's been so sad.
Krish NAik: Mmm… right now I can't… yes, it's getting loaded.
Krish NAik: Okay, see, see, see, see, see, see. The… it's… what is the error it's telling?
Krish NAik: The repository with name rackText2SQL does not exist. Okay, now show me.
Krish NAik: Eoricia repo?
Krish NAik: red.
Krish NAik: hyphen text, rag text to SQL is here.
Krish NAik: Alright, show me your deploy.yml file.
Krish NAik: Open the text editor.
Balaji Rengan: I'll show it to you.
Krish NAik: Okay, so here, you have rag hyphen text to SQL, here also this is fine. Other than that, there is no other place. That's why. Rag Text2SQL, this is there, but it's telling the repository does not exist, because I know the repo has got created rag text to SQL,
Krish NAik: This is a private trip for, 6-3, this is fine.
Krish NAik: EVRI… URI is not required right now, exactly.
Krish NAik: Recall, from the repository name, it will pick up the initial URL.
Krish NAik: Alright, now switch back to the, that page of GitHub Actions.
Balaji Rengan: Data, I mean?
Krish NAik: Huh, because here, rad text to SQL is there. You scroll below.
Krish NAik: Nope.
Krish NAik: Because here only it's telling that the repository… The reason failed…
Krish NAik: To push ECR, write text to SQL…
Krish NAik: Okay, the repository with the name RadTextraSQL does not exist in the registry with the ID.
Krish NAik: Sharing credentials, auth…
Krish NAik: really, like, does this user have this now? That is the main thing, because here it's telling…
Krish NAik: Auth issue, finally it's coming. Sharing credentials, and then finally done.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: check, because, open your CLI.
Krish NAik: Okay, and show me, like, all those commands that I have to…
Krish NAik: Because I feel that there is some issue with respect to credentials only.
Balaji Rengan: And it seems like… Scroll over to these old…
Krish NAik: Because the command that I have, given, directly copy-paste from there.
Balaji Rengan: Which command you want to place?
Krish NAik: Deploy? Yes. When you created the ECR, that part. First, your ECR is… Other than that…
Balaji Rengan: Depositories we want to…
Krish NAik: Yes, only that print, yes, do this at least. Do this, yes, this one. Don't use export, directly pick up after dollar after bracket. Directly, the command will be starting from AWS. Nothing without brackets. Don't use any brackets, start from AWS, yes, and before bracket, copy that and paste and show.
Krish NAik: For ECR, there is no rule that I have specifically created, because yes, right now, as I can see here, for this particular user, yes, this is it.
Krish NAik: Mmm…
Krish NAik: And right now, I'm not passing any URI, neither in secrets. Directly, I'm just passing the name. Based on that name, it will be picked up, the URL. That's the logic in deploy.wyoming.
Krish NAik: They show, okay, alright, find this part.
Krish NAik: Just wait. What is that minor issue I'm thinking that is coming?
Krish NAik: Downloading succeed.
Krish NAik: Have you tried to, do that AWSCCR get login password? Try to log in.
Balaji Rengan: Okay, I do.
Krish NAik: Try to do the authentication, like, Docker 2 is here. Let me see if the authentication is getting passed on.
Balaji Rengan: Okay, so…
Krish NAik: That login succeed.
Balaji Rengan: Login now.
Krish NAik: Oh.
Balaji Rengan: Is that available in the DeployMD, or…
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, it is available, yes, this command. With your ECRI that you bought it, let me show that to you.
Balaji Rengan: As exported. Okay, let me check this.
Krish NAik: Because the first thing it says checks the verification, it tries to log in. According to deploy.yml, this command should work.
Balaji Rengan: Yeah, this gives an error. Logging during point… Thank you.
Balaji Rengan: In which it is bad, right, but…
Krish NAik: No, no, no, your dollar ECR URI is there, no, that variable updates to your ECR URI. That is above 637.
Balaji Rengan: I've updated, yeah.
Balaji Rengan: Let's see it.
Balaji Rengan: This one very tight.
Krish NAik: Okay, ECO, you have exported as a variable, then it's fine.
Krish NAik: So check that, because this logging should work.
Balaji Rengan: Well, this username and password should be changed, or…
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, nothing. Only that ECR URI.
Balaji Rengan: That needs to be changed.
Balaji Rengan: It's not working.
Krish NAik: Because this batch request is coming, because of that, because, again, if you look into the logs, okay, so just wait, I will tell you.
Krish NAik: That part with respect to,
Krish NAik: Okay, so verify ECR login. That part, you can…
Krish NAik: get it in your, deployment. A very specific step is there. You can skip that, because locally, also, it should work, you should get a login succeed.
Krish NAik: Okay, otherwise, go back to GitHub Actions, and check, there, what is that, you are getting. GitHub Actions, yes, go at the top, before build tag. First couple, the login verification to ECR, yes. Collapse this one, scroll above, scroll above, above, above, above, above.
Krish NAik: above, above, above, log into ECR. Yes, there will be one part, log into Amazon ECR.
Balaji Rengan: Yeah.
Krish NAik: Yes, this one.
Krish NAik: Okay, log into Amazon ECR action, verify. When that verification is done, yes, that is the main part.
Krish NAik: Because here, it successfully logged in into ECR. If it has logged in into ECR,
Krish NAik: Now, that's the thing, because here it's telling that the registration is successful, but in your local… just check with the command again, one second.
Balaji Rengan: On the comment?
Krish NAik: And yes, this one.
Krish NAik: Here, also, it shows login steps. Wait, wait, wait, wait, I think it will show…
Krish NAik: Are you sure, with respect to the regions and others, everything, it is US Eastward only?
Balaji Rengan: I used to… actually, I'm using IES use 2. US East 2 is the region, is my region.
Krish NAik: Okay, go back to your script.
Krish NAik: of deploy.viami.
Balaji Rengan: Yeah. Oh…
Krish NAik: What is the environment variable written there?
Balaji Rengan: Oh, it's written ES1, so that's the problem.
Balaji Rengan: Okay, okay, okay. Yeah, I'll take it. Thank you, thank you. I'll try again, yeah.
Krish NAik: It becomes very confusing for me also. Like, that's why, like, I… if you change even one parting, you have to look into the script. That's why I told chain line number 9 and 10, I didn't thought, like, others are using different regions, but always look into… here, these three things are hard-coded for everyone.
Balaji Rengan: Okay, your ACR repo name?
Krish NAik: and then your lambda function, these 3 things are hard-coded.
Balaji Rengan: Because you can expose these things, really, it doesn't matter.
Krish NAik: Alright, now coming to San Rajanth.
Krish NAik: Okay, so this part is done. Rajat, I will add you to panelist.
Krish NAik: Okay, because I know this deployment will be a bit confusing, but, it's fine. You will understand each thing step by step.
Krish NAik: Jeez.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: I'll allow a law click on a loan.
Krish NAik: First time, it looks like you are sharing for Mac.
Rajat Khanna: One minute, I think I need to share other screen.
Krish NAik: Alright, stop sharing and start sharing that screen.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, it's visible, right?
Krish NAik: Yes, I can see. So, in your case, this is going. Till now, where is the last time you got? Yeah. I can see that red mark.
Rajat Khanna: Now, no red is there, same thing.
Rajat Khanna: So, it's still… here it still goes, and from here it fails?
Krish NAik: ACS2, this is fine, there is no error till now.
Krish NAik: But, like, once this fails, after that, some error will be coming, you know, into your log.
Rajat Khanna: No, it doesn't get filled if I have means previously, so if last in.
Krish NAik: Show me the previous errors, show me the previous errors there.
Krish NAik: Okay, Melinda will come, just wait.
Krish NAik: Show me the… see, here it failed directly, because no identity, authorization, so your login to Amazon is here fade.
Rajat Khanna: But from here, if I am checking, so everything is getting passed, but the last function, function execution, doesn't went through. I have also…
Krish NAik: Show me that login succeed, login succeed, but… Logins, I think that,
Krish NAik: ECR login, that, command. Try to copy it from the Markdown file, and use your own URI.
Krish NAik: How about this one?
Krish NAik: Yes, this one.
Rajat Khanna: Is your… I have written here this one, right?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, correct.
Krish NAik: Then copy this and paste it through me here, login succeed.
Krish NAik: Okay? In your local, it's working. Alright, now, go back to your AWS, and, the name is that you have given track text to SQL only. Show me your deploy.yml.
Krish NAik: Okay, US East 1, rack text to SQL. Now, this is fine.
Krish NAik: I'm gonna do one push.
Krish NAik: the AMD64 or the latest. We can push both DJ, but right now, my priority was AMD64, okay? Otherwise, actually, during the deployment, the latest one will be picked up.
Krish NAik: Alright, so… This is where US East 1, I can see. And also…
Rajat Khanna: I think in your… there was some image ID, there is no image ID here.
Krish NAik: Image index, type image index, it's shown.
Krish NAik: Here… Because there, during the deployment, okay, now.
Krish NAik: Generally, okay, go back to your GitHub.
Krish NAik: You know, that CICT page.
Krish NAik: Because, see, logging to ECR, if it's failing.
Krish NAik: EWS Actions is your logging. This generally can happen if you have.
Rajat Khanna: This girl.
Krish NAik: boss.
Krish NAik: something wrong in your secrets. If there is something wrong in your secrets.
Rajat Khanna: Now, see, here it is still going, and it is stuck here.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, now.
Krish NAik: Go at the top, top, top, top, top, top, because then the verification is done, no, in this bit.
Krish NAik: See, verify is your login. So here, the login is successful. Yes, I can see.
Rajat Khanna: So this is fine, the build is taking place, there is no issue with the build.
Rajat Khanna: No, no, so same, the last build, the failed build I show you, it was at night, so it's, like, 2.41 AM. Okay, so now, this was, again, okay, I tried for 1.32 AM, so that is still going on, and this will is still going on.
Krish NAik: Which one is going on?
Rajat Khanna: this Git file, and ECR name change. So, if I go to this Git file, and go to deploy…
Rajat Khanna: So, see, it is still, going on, and I have pushed this in morning, like, 1.30am.
Rajat Khanna: So, it is…
Krish NAik: Oh, right. You were telling that, so… It's not getting pushed.
Krish NAik: Because if the verify to, like, ECR login is successful, as I can see in the logs, it means that the image should be pushed, because there is nothing so much, like, anything.
Rajat Khanna: Image is posted today, see? 9.51.
Rajat Khanna: from the local, what I have done, so from here, this, this local push, because of that, this image was pushed, not because of… from here.
Rajat Khanna: Because Builder didn't get.
Krish NAik: That's all right.
Rajat Khanna: So, that is.
Krish NAik: Well, wait.
Rajat Khanna: Hush did not know.
Krish NAik: do one thing, delete all the images in your ECR, and redeploy it and show me, like, what is that? Because I want to do that particular verification. Delete all the images.
Krish NAik: Okay, now just do a small change anywhere, it'll mark down file anywhere, and just, do a push.
Krish NAik: Okay, now let me see.
Krish NAik: All this tracking really takes time, okay? Milan, in your case, what is the issue that you are facing? You can let me know.
Krish NAik: build catcher, that is fine. For your next deployment, it is faster. If you get an error, you can let me know. People who are getting there, then I will add you in.
Rajat Khanna: So, from here…
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, so from here, it will go till the build, and then the build will go on and on, and from after, I think.
Krish NAik: Okay, on and on, let me see, like, on and on is fine, there is no issue.
Rajat Khanna: But after 6, 7, or 8 minutes, from here, it got failed. So when, if the equipment…
Krish NAik: Let me track this one, okay? Because if I don't see the tracking, it's very hard for me also, because I need the exact error, why it is not getting pushed, that's why.
Rajat Khanna: Do I need to zoom?
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it is visible.
Krish NAik: just fruit.
Krish NAik: Others, please let me know.
Krish NAik: In the meantime, Melind, push, I get the same error, not supported. Doing GitHub action and still in progress. Like, okay, just wait, Milind, then we'll…
Krish NAik: Military Durant.
Krish NAik: Because it's mainly the tracking of the logs only through
Krish NAik: Here only I can actually understand it.
Krish NAik: Santosh, then… Santosh, you can tell me your errors in the chat, so that it becomes easier for me. Yes, yes, I will check you.
Rajat Khanna: Well, just to, just to understand, like, from here, the image is built, and then we run the command, push latest docker image. So, that is already done. And after that, when we, run the lambda, command, so it shows an error. So, why is that? Lambda error?
Krish NAik: in your… in your ECR URI, at least one image should be there. That's why. At least one. If it is blank, then it comes.
Krish NAik: Because you are actually building the Lambda function with the image, if there is no image only, that's why the error is coming.
Rajat Khanna: But now, just now, means previously we checked, the image was there, because we pushed from here, from the local to the Git,
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, that was manual. Okay, so just wait, let me see, like, where it's getting started. Manit, you can also share your screen. You are in panelists, both the screens, I can look into Paramith.
Krish NAik: Santos, you can let me know your issue in the meantime in the chat room.
Rajat Khanna: Every Dubai.
Rajat Khanna: Beautiful.
Krish NAik: So, Roger, yes, I can see the image came here.
Krish NAik: No. This was… you right now deleted, I think this is the image?
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, yeah, so it… I ran this lambda function previously, but just now you told me to delete so that we can check from here.
Krish NAik: No, no, this is your ECR, this is nothing related to your Lambda.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Go back to your logs. Show me the logs only. I think it will be better. Writing layer, just wait.
Krish NAik: Mitesh, just wait. Mitesh, I will come to you also, one by one.
Krish NAik: All right, okay, this is… okay, I'm looking into millions… sorry, sorry, sorry, I got confused.
Krish NAik: Just wait. In your case, this is going on, fine. Let it go. Where you see that red mark? Okay, I will look into that error. In the meantime, let me look into Melind. Melind, writing… okay, now, in your case, there is no error. This is… the build is going on. This is fine.
Krish NAik: Writing the layer.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. This image, today only, no. It got, I think.
Krish NAik: It's 31st, January 31st, so it has to be 1st February. Till now, the latest one has not been pushed in, so wait.
Krish NAik: I think according to the data.
Krish NAik: Okay, in your case, the error is definite, it is with respect to ECR directly. I can see.
Krish NAik: So, just wait until she will come.
Krish NAik: In the meantime, let me add one more person I think I can look into. Mitesh, also, I will add it, okay?
Krish NAik: Because if the function gets created, it's only updating the Lambda function, and automatically the deployment will be done.
Krish NAik: Just check your audio when you submit.
Krish NAik: Santosh will add invitation will… Oh, okay.
milind kulkarni: Paul, can you hear me, Paul, or no?
Krish NAik: BSIP.
milind kulkarni: million.
Krish NAik: Yes, Melinda, I can hear now.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, just to… just to show you, this build, if you are able to see, this one is red, and it is, saying failed 40 minutes ago. But I… this build started, night at 1.30 AM.
Rajat Khanna: So now, if I have started that at 1.30 AM, it is failing 40 minutes ago, and still there is no error message, it's just stopped here, exporting layer.
Krish NAik: Alright, exporting yourself.
Rajat Khanna: Gloves.
Krish NAik: So clean.
Rajat Khanna: So now, means, just to give you reference, the thing that we have just, pushed, to make the changes. So, this build will fail, I think, within 2 to 3 minutes, but error message will not come.
Rajat Khanna: Because, for that, that I pushed in 1.30 AM, that also, is not showing any error message.
Krish NAik: Because without an error message, it's very hard, actually. So, like, now I'm feeling from GitHub's side.
Krish NAik: Issue, or what exactly?
Krish NAik: Generally, there should not be any issue with respect to GitHub actions, but again.
Rajat Khanna: If I try to push it manually again.
Rajat Khanna: And try this, lambda function again, we can check.
Krish NAik: Then, see, then if the image is available manually from the UI also, you can create the Lambda function. But…
Krish NAik: Manual things for test the automated part. If it's not working, then do that manual thing.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, okay.
Krish NAik: Martha? Yes.
milind kulkarni: Hey, Bob, can you hear me? Yes, ma'am.
Krish NAik: a million.
milind kulkarni: Yeah, so, so, so GitHub action is going on, but, command line, I get the same error saying that not supported, right?
milind kulkarni: I think GitHub action, I can wait for some more time to finish.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, just wait for the GitHub Actions, because GitHub Actions should do it automatically for you. From local, you do need to do that.
Krish NAik: So, that's why…
Krish NAik: Should… okay, in the meantime, ask, first of all, Santosh, you tell me, your issue is much more with respect to ECR, I think. Santosh, quickly tell me.
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, Paul.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Santosh Umargi: First time I push, no, in the mo… In this?
Santosh Umargi: So, it fell, that stage.
Santosh Umargi: failed to solve, failed to push this rack test to SQL doc.
Krish NAik: Show more, show more, click on show more. It's telling the repository does not exist directly. It means that check the region part, or check that repo part. Right now, the deployment that you have done, again, the same thing.
Krish NAik: Rec, text-to-SQL doc.
Krish NAik: So.
milind kulkarni: What's…
Krish NAik: Right now, which we are doing 10.
milind kulkarni: Deploy.yaml, right? Deploy.yaml has dash doc, actually.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes.
Santosh Umargi: Ha, right now, in this, I changed that, it is going on,
milind kulkarni: Okay, yeah.
Krish NAik: Okay…
Santosh Umargi: Okay, same error, crack test to SQL.
Krish NAik: rack text to SQL, show me now in AWS, that, UI.
Krish NAik: Just open ECR and show me that.
Rajat Khanna: So, Paul, see, the deployment is red.
Krish NAik: Where is the report?
Krish NAik: Whose screen I'm seeing? This is Santosh only.
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, yeah, huh, mine only.
Krish NAik: So, where is the report that you are making the push?
Santosh Umargi: Actually, I deleted just now that error came, no? I deleted directly by saying, you said, no, just now that to someone.
Krish NAik: No, no, you don't need to… see, neither I deleted the repo, you can keep the repo, doesn't matter, but you're not getting charged. If you don't have the repo, for sure. First of all, create the repo, then again, redeploy.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay. So in, GitHub Action, that step is not there, creating repo and…
Krish NAik: No, no, no, creating the repo, I have not done it there.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay. Okay, I will… I will create the repo, and we'll try.
Krish NAik: Alright, Mitesh, quickly you tell me your issue.
Mitesh Shah: Yeah, so I'm not doing a push through GitHub right now, I was just doing a manual build and following the commands. I was stuck,
Mitesh Shah: on the level there, when I was looking into Docker push, I did a push to ECR, but when I'm describing the images, I can see the images on my AWS console, but not able to see it on my,
Mitesh Shah: That, that is telling me that that, particular report.
Krish NAik: Share your screen, share your screen, Mitesh, share your screen, and just keep the mic a little bit closer.
Mitesh Shah: Raul, you also have raised your hand.
Mitesh Shah: Is it better now?
Krish NAik: Yes, so Mitesh, share your screen.
Mitesh Shah: I'm shutting.
Krish NAik: Share your screen and show me, because it should not be like that. You can see it there, it cannot see it here.
Mitesh Shah: Are you able to see the screen?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, I can see.
Mitesh Shah: So, if I see this, this command, specifically.
Krish NAik: Because I can see a blank monitor. It means that only the wallpaper I can see, no other window that I can see.
Mitesh Shah: Okay.
Krish NAik: Yes, now I can see. Fine.
Mitesh Shah: Yeah, so I'm getting this error, where an error occurred for this, the particular repository does not exist.
Mitesh Shah: But I have.
Krish NAik: First of all, show that AWS Describe, AWS ECR, Describe repositories, you can do that.
Krish NAik: At least it will tell you, you know, what are the repositories that you have.
Mitesh Shah: Describe repositories.
Krish NAik: Mmm, AWS describe hyphen repositories.
Krish NAik: AWS ECR, don't keep before, describe, no hyphen.
Krish NAik: Yes, repositories.
Krish NAik: Okay, so it's telling that you have a single repository, and the name is Rack UA System.
Mitesh Shah: But I can see…
Mitesh Shah: I go to repositories, I can see too.
Krish NAik: Rag… now the user, it really matters, like, are you using the same user? Because, see, it should be there.
Mitesh Shah: I actually want to use it.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: because.
Mitesh Shah: I only have one user.
Rajat Khanna: It didn't know, it was like.
Krish NAik: From the command line, also, it should be visible.
Rajat Khanna: Have a blessed weekend, Emma.
Mitesh Shah: Not sure, but I only have… Good morning, dude.
Krish NAik: Okay, only one user, only UI.
Mitesh Shah: Ugh.
Krish NAik: And you were using, your main region as US East 1 only, no?
Krish NAik: Because now I'm thinking exactly right, text to SQL hyphen doc, but when you are trying to describe the recoverable phrase, then also it's not showing.
Mitesh Shah: I did even this one.
Mitesh Shah: This worked.
Mitesh Shah: That did not give me any issue.
Krish NAik: Alright, can you do the other ones? Probably, like, describe repositories generally shows all the repositories. Otherwise, go to that, markdown file, okay, and describe repositories, you can, check that. Hyphen, hyphen repository name query, go to that markdown file that I've shared, new deploy.md.
Krish NAik: Because here also, yes, our… yes, take this one.
Krish NAik: Generally, AWS Describe shows all the
Krish NAik: Ones, but let's look here.
Mitesh Shah: This one, right? This comes.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: Because if you have text-to-SQL doc, it does not exist.
Krish NAik: Just be sure when you are using that you are past the correct URL. I think that is the bare minimum requirement here.
Krish NAik: Aws describe…
Mitesh Shah: These are the commands that I use.
Mitesh Shah: I don't think so I've anywhere used anything else.
Mitesh Shah: obey.
Krish NAik: Now, these are Docker build, Docker push. This is ECR.
Krish NAik: Get login… Even if you try to do a login, like RAT2SQL, 1…
Krish NAik: I don't think there will be an AMD in your RAT2SQL doc, if the name is there.
Krish NAik: then only it will come. Because in the output, you will be getting something like that.
Mitesh Shah: I have this. I had the belt that I purchased.
Krish NAik: Okay, the manual build that you have taken, but from the CLI, at least that, repo should be visible.
Krish NAik: Because we are working with private repos.
Mitesh Shah: Judy?
Krish NAik: Hmm.
Krish NAik: goes to it.
Mitesh Shah: when I'm using the same URL.
Krish NAik: Alright, the repo URL is there, but it's not showing you the repos.
Krish NAik: Not really, like, huh… AWS Describe repository is not working.
Krish NAik: When calling describe images with respect to text, this is also not working.
Krish NAik: Really, because with ECR, you don't need anything, like, no role, nothing, directly.
Mitesh Shah: I'm also not sure, there's only one way I can delete it, and I can push it in the RACQA system. It's required.
Krish NAik: You have created it from the UI, or manually created it?
Krish NAik: Like, from command line.
Mitesh Shah: Perfectly, yes, I created it manually.
Krish NAik: Alright, so millionth working, all images pushed to ECR, updating the lambda function.
Krish NAik: Alright, now this is fine. If you don't have the lambda function, then that would… yes, if you create the function, then that will be updated.
Krish NAik: But, wait till that point, because this part is fine, till now, for you.
Krish NAik: Because, just create a new ECR repo, no, in front of it.
Krish NAik: dooded.
Krish NAik: Already the commands are there.
Krish NAik: Okay, just give a new name.
Krish NAik: A bubb, ba-ba. On top.
Krish NAik: Yes. Okay, and write text to SQL, give a different name in your case. Add something like server, serverless, just like me to update.
Krish NAik: iPhone, it's telling in command line, it shows EU North, but in AWS EY, it shows Virginia.
Krish NAik: Okay, North Virginia, in command line, it shows for Mithay Shiva Telen.
Krish NAik: Okay, for Mitesh. Mitesh, just show me, because somebody is telling in the chat.
Krish NAik: In your command line, it shows EU North.
Krish NAik: Do you in North London.
Mitesh Shah: As you know.
Krish NAik: do, first of all, see, because right now, I feel that
Krish NAik: Do an AWS configure and show me.
Krish NAik: Because, see, these configurations are something like one-time stuff, so show me that here your AWS configure, for which region that you have configured, that is much more important.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Mitesh Shah: 50 ID.
Mitesh Shah: Give me a minute, Doug. I will reshare it, just give me a second.
Mitesh Shah: I'm going to take some…
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. Yes, yes, take your time. In the meantime, Rajat, in your case, What happened?
Krish NAik: 10 minutes break, I'm looking into queries only, Anud. I'm not doing anything.
Krish NAik: Because, for Melinda it works, so I know that for others also it should work, if everything is fine.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, so Paul, same thing, like, deploys failed, and it is still stuck at, build.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, we'll be talking about that, okay? So, deploy, build, tag, push, but before that one, you can go back.
Krish NAik: Now, what is the error that has been shown there?
Krish NAik: No error.
Krish NAik: Okay, this is no error, but it keeps on running and running.
Rajat Khanna: Yes.
Rajat Khanna: You're just okay.
Krish NAik: Well, without an error, how to debug.
Rajat Khanna: So…
Krish NAik: Because exactly the issue is from GitHub Actions side.
Krish NAik: Or from which side?
Krish NAik: The image has not been pushed.
Rajat Khanna: Hmm.
Rajat Khanna: We're stuck.
Rajat Khanna: It's stuck here now. It shows exporting image, exporting layer, and it is stuck. So, image is not being exported, and deploy gets filled.
Krish NAik: ECR is not a paid service, initially, like, he can't do it for free also.
Krish NAik: Other than that.
Rajat Khanna: Mitesh, got the issue, it is about the region, redoing all the stuff. Guys, please, you see, even I'm in India, I'm in the easiest one.
Krish NAik: Okay, just stick to a single region, always, for your entire course. It becomes much easier, rather than changing the regions. Alright, Rahul, I think you are… you can unmute yourself. You raised your hand.
Rajat Khanna: Hey, Paul.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Rahul Parihar: But I…
Rahul Parihar: I'd like to share the screen, and… sorry, I've joined in late today, but I did some of the work yesterday.
Krish NAik: Okay, follow the document, no?
Krish NAik: Okay. Because in your case, Rajat, it's really, like, if I don't know the error, it's very hard for me to tell the error what is the error.
Krish NAik: That is the other way around, do a manual push, Rajat, okay? For now, do it.
Krish NAik: Because, again, if I change the ECR, that's how there we are out. Yes, I can see your screen route, tell me.
Rahul: Okay.
Rahul: So, my image is pushed…
Krish NAik: Alright.
Rahul: And, I just… Did a debug of…
Rahul: I just made some change in the… in the Docker… oops.
Rahul: I just re-pushed it.
Rahul: So…
Rahul: I got this confirmation that, yeah, the function is created, but when I'm trying to create the lambda function.
Rahul: Are we there yet? Like, you know, creating a lambda function?
Krish NAik: No, no, no, if the Lambda function, you got that success, it looks like, for you, it was a success, open AWS, go to Lambda, check if the function is created or not. Directly from the UI, you can check in.
Krish NAik: Because I think it should be checked, according to your message that I saw. So, I am feeling that it should be there. Yes, it is there, fine.
Krish NAik: Listen?
Rahul: So we are till… we are till here, right? Right now, I wanted to.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. You are in the correct phase. In the next part, I will be just updating the function. For this lambda, we need the environment variables. So below, if you follow the document, you will see that I'll be setting
Krish NAik: a list. So if you check the configuration part, right now there are no ENVs. So you are in the correct.
Rahul: Okay.
Krish NAik: All right. Now, Rajat, in your case, try to do it manually.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, I have posted, if you can see, so it is there now in the, ECR, but I have filed the test, so it is showing the error if I do…
Rajat Khanna: Secret?
Krish NAik: in your… Q.
Rajat Khanna: Yes, same.
Krish NAik: Latest is also not working, this is also not working.
Rajat Khanna: Yes.
Krish NAik: Mmm… the image manifest config, or the layertype for the source image.
Rajat Khanna: I do.
Krish NAik: Why it's selling 12344, this is your, ACR URI.
Rajat Khanna: Yes, yes. So, this is my ACR.
Krish NAik: Okay, got it, got it. Here, it's written eco… Alright.
Krish NAik: Because if the image is available.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. This create lambda function is not working. Create it manually from email.
Krish NAik: Open Lambda, and then do that.
Santosh Umargi: Paul, it got, succeeded at that stage, it is brilliant.
Krish NAik: All right.
Santosh Umargi: In the local, no, I had created an image, but, like, during…
Santosh Umargi: You can see these 4 images that got created yesterday.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Santosh Umargi: But today I tried manually, you know, through command. It is not.
Krish NAik: Good.
Santosh Umargi: Bring it.
Krish NAik: Show me, like, Mac, which command didn't work for you.
Santosh Umargi: That, the… after this, we cultivated, doc… everything, Docker also, image also got pushed, and…
Santosh Umargi: I can't see here.
Krish NAik: Tell me the error. What is the error?
Santosh Umargi: Error, okay.
Rajat Khanna: Paul.
Santosh Umargi: Lambda create, huh? During Lambda creation only, I was getting the… that… that image, it was not pulling.
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now.
Santosh Umargi: You asked, no, to change that, the here, no?
Krish NAik: Attack to later stairs.
Krish NAik: After that, it worked, I can see the logs. This is fine, there is no problem.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, so right now, I'm testing through the… this, no, GitHub Actions only.
Santosh Umargi: So it is, yeah, it got succeeded, yeah.
Santosh Umargi: So manually, after this, manually, I had to create the function, no? Right?
Krish NAik: Yes, for that, the command is there. The function is there. Later on, we'll be updating the function manually.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay.
Krish NAik: Alrighty, yes, Rajat, what are you telling?
Rajat Khanna: So, I have choose image container, given the function, choose the image.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes, yes. These are the only.
Rajat Khanna: Where do I need to change AI?
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no way Aaron. Your image is based on X2, that's me. Additional configuration check.
Krish NAik: Because later on, I think, once it gets created, you can actually… Lambda default, this is fine.
Krish NAik: Function URL, later on I'll be enable it, or right now, you can enable this one.
Krish NAik: Tag, okay.
Krish NAik: No, no, disable it for now. Disable it for now, later on through commands. Create the function.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine, I think, majorly for most of you, it's saying the image manifest config, okay, the same error that you were getting.
Krish NAik: Now, I'm feeling there is some issue with respect to the image that got uploaded then, because manually, if you were doing it.
Krish NAik: This is SHE… RA, the image manifest config, or the media type of this image. There is some issue.
Krish NAik: Just open your ECR and show me.
Rajat Khanna: study, or…
Krish NAik: I think you have that, AMD64 tagged.
Rajat Khanna: God knows.
Rajat Khanna: honey!
Krish NAik: Okay, this is the image and text, it should be image.
Krish NAik: This should be mesh.
Krish NAik: It should not engage index, first of all.
Rajat Khanna: So, if it is showing image here, there is no name here.
Rajat Khanna: Any issue, because the size is same.
Krish NAik: Timing is also same.
Rahul: I faced the same problem, Paul. I resolved it by changing the tag image.
Rahul: Command. Retagging, yeah, I just sent the command.
Rahul: If he runs that command, it will… it should fix the problem.
Krish NAik: This and those… You have added OK, because the command is pretty much sane, only it looks to me.
Rajat Khanna: Toker bill.
Krish NAik: They were in panelists, so we can't sleep.
Rajat Khanna: cases.
Rahul: Oh.
Rahul: Okay.
Krish NAik: Okay, now you have done the tagging, okay, Raja, try it out. But in your case, why GitHub Actions is failing? No, this is really strange.
Krish NAik: Like, though it is running, then also it is failing.
Rahul: Yeah, that dot, yeah, that dot is required, yeah.
Rahul: Just try running this and re-tag and push it again.
Krish NAik: Last time you used the .NE.
Rajat Khanna: Yes, yes.
Krish NAik: No kidding.
Rahul: Yo.
Rajat Khanna: You see, it's… it's already there.
Krish NAik: Yes, it's picked up from the catcher, that's why the build was faster.
Krish NAik: Hmm.
Rahul: And now run the Docker tag.
Rajat Khanna: Are you…
Krish NAik: Delete, clean your ECR, okay, and then so that fresh images comes.
Rahul: No, no, the…
Krish NAik: The docker tag command. Tag.
Rahul: Someone in the.
Krish NAik: Check the chat, check, check the chat, check the chat, Raul has shared.
Rajat Khanna: Okay…
Krish NAik: But my mind is the same, only, like, is your URL latest, MD64, after that you were doing the push, yes.
Rahul: No, not this one.
Krish NAik: Below that.
Rahul: Below, below the one, yeah.
Krish NAik: Docker tag command is there, yes. Okay, the first line that you have.
Krish NAik: The first one, yes.
Rajat Khanna: We're DC on…
Krish NAik: Because the command is exactly the same that he's using, okay, but let's see the tags.
Krish NAik: Would that.
Rahul: define the ECR URL, export it, and, you know, that's fine.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, account ID…
Rahul: And, so I got the lambda function URL, but when I'm hitting that URL, Paul.
Rahul: It's, it's giving me my thinking.
Rajat Khanna: The thing popped this I need to change.
Krish NAik: Just wait.
Krish NAik: Few things are there, you have to update, and those things.
Krish NAik: Once this step is done, then I think after 10 minutes, we'll be done.
Krish NAik: Just do it. So, first I'll, push this, this one? First tag, then push.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Rahul: Yeah, first tag and then push.
Rajat Khanna: That was odd enough.
Rajat Khanna: Dang.
Rajat Khanna: And then… Push…
Krish NAik: Only one line, one line. There are two commands, rocker, push, push.
Rajat Khanna: So, one is latest, one is AMD 64.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Rajat Khanna: So, only later style push.
Krish NAik: You know, you have the letters, then push…
Krish NAik: I think if both the things are tagged.
Rajat Khanna: AMD64 as well.
Krish NAik: Yes, I actually did, two tags.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Now, test.
Krish NAik: God created.
Rajat Khanna: Hmm.
Rajat Khanna: Mmm.
Rajat Khanna: Jane?
Krish NAik: Image came, no, that's fine.
Krish NAik: There was no emergency that got updated.
Krish NAik: Fine, fine, fine. But in your GitHub Actions, that are the main thing. This should be automatically done from GitHub Actions.
Krish NAik: Because manually you have done it, if it is working, then…
Krish NAik: through your CICD also, it should work.
Rajat Khanna: So now it is there.
Rajat Khanna: But from the GitHub, it is just, stuck.
Krish NAik: This is fine, this is fine. Because once it's got created, this is fine, next we'll be adding the environment variables and other stuff.
Rajat Khanna: kidding.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. So I think, Major, you guys can be in the panelists, okay?
Krish NAik: Now, I think you can stop sharing your screen.
Krish NAik: Alright, now let me start buying one.
Krish NAik: Update.
Rahul: Did you start the workflow, Paul?
Krish NAik: No, no, no, this is for a different, I think the lambda function here is different, and there it is different, just wait.
Krish NAik: Probably, let me check till I'm done.
Krish NAik: Let me check my deploy, did I update that, file name?
Krish NAik: Deploy what is exactly. So right now, Lambda function is serverless.
Krish NAik: Okay…
Krish NAik: Already here, it's coming. This is fine, then.
Krish NAik: Alright, so, before this, it's fine, because we are, in… let me just go back to Markdown file. For everybody, the lambda function is created or not.
Krish NAik: Please let me know that part.
Krish NAik: Because the lambda function should be created. Once the lambda function is created, then in the next step.
Krish NAik: Like, you can use this, like, generally it takes 1 minute, okay, under 60 seconds, your function will be active. For most of you, I think this step is done.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright, lambda function you are getting, then Arun it's good, no issues. Then comes verification of the function, they will be getting a table like this. Okay, so… okay. Now, this is where I allow the course, but I think for, this is the place where I'll be creating the
Krish NAik: function URL, okay? So you can use this way, or you can only copy this particular command.
Krish NAik: Okay? So, right now, what I will do…
Krish NAik: I have created, as, multiple functions, so I will not use this serverless, rather than I will use only the server one, okay? So this is the first step to create the function.
Krish NAik: So let me just, go here, okay? So, there is a server, okay, write text to SQL server, so this is the Lambda function that I will be working with.
Krish NAik: So let me go to my terminal… where is my terminal? Terminal?
Krish NAik: Okay, I think my terminal is here, I think, yes.
Krish NAik: First of all, we have to create the lambda function. Okay, let me remove serverless from here. Okay, only the server course I have allowed. Okay, otherwise I will be getting authentication right now, none.
Krish NAik: Query, okay, function URL, output, okay, I think. Let me hit enter.
Krish NAik: Alright, so this is the lambda function.
Krish NAik: This is a function URL of the lambda that got created, okay?
Krish NAik: So… Till this point, I think everybody has done it, yes or no, please tell me.
Krish NAik: Now, these two things, you need to add the permissions.
Krish NAik: to your, function URL. In 2026, two things that has been changed. So, very specifically, you need to do these two things. Okay, so one is adding the, permission, okay, for invoking. So, the first one.
Krish NAik: Okay, and I think, with respect to my first
Krish NAik: Invoking one, let me change the name again here, server.
Krish NAik: This is the new function that I have created. Alright.
Krish NAik: The first permission that got added.
Krish NAik: Now, I will come to the…
Krish NAik: Second permission, which is the Lambda input.
Krish NAik: Okay, the 2026 update one.
Krish NAik: So, again, here, server…
Krish NAik: Alright, these two things are done.
Krish NAik: Hmm… I think I have added the permissions. Once the permissions are added.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I don't think I'll be okay, so… let me just, verify.
Krish NAik: my lambda function config once.
Krish NAik: For my sarfur.
Krish NAik: Alright, I can see the function URL with me.
Krish NAik: And this is the, SQL 100.
Krish NAik: Let me see from here, can I access the function URL or not?
Krish NAik: Alright, so I can see, yes…
Krish NAik: So, after adding, so you need those two permissions. Without those two permissions, you cannot actually see the application.
Krish NAik: Okay, so here, if I go, if I write slash tops…
Krish NAik: So, I think, yes, this is coming.
Krish NAik: Alright, others also please do the verification, because now this is my new Lambda function, and everything, I have done it from scratch. So others also please test it.
Krish NAik: you need these two permissions. Without that permission, simply will be getting there.
Rahul: Yeah.
Rahul: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Okay,
Krish NAik: Just wait, just wait. Actually, we have not passed. In your case, if I go to the lambda, I think,
Krish NAik: Just wait, if I look into my major configuration, environment variables… So right now, can you see? There are no environment variables?
Krish NAik: And we need to set the environment variables, because till now, this is blank. So my… I know the application is up. From here, I can see the Swagger UI, so I know that. But my main application won't be working, okay? So for that, what we have to do, we have to pass the entire list
Krish NAik: Of, all the secrets.
Krish NAik: So, coming to my secrets part…
Krish NAik: Okay, so I think we'll be having one command.
Krish NAik: to update your Lambda function with all of your environment variables.
Krish NAik: Okay? You have to run this one. So, right now, everything is a variable, so just be sure that you have the correct values. And even pass these, I think, optional ones also. Upstash readies, this is not included in this command.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just pass that thing. You need to actually update your Lambda function with the environment variables.
Krish NAik: Everybody?
Krish NAik: First of all, can you see the Swagger UI or not? Because at least you will, can get that,
Krish NAik: So, at least this thing… how many of you can see this part? Swagger UI is up? Fine.
Krish NAik: Now, I will be updating the environment.
Rahul: All you need to do.
Krish NAik: For you with spelling, it's forbidden.
Rahul: Oh, no, no, no worries. It's, it, it just came up, yeah. It's working.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright. Okay, now, pretty much a big command that I'll be passing. Okay, as per this… okay, so with all the environment variables, just be sure you are, adding this op stash, ready URL and OPIC AI key here only. Put comma, and below that.
Krish NAik: Okay, so let me just go here, I will just, pass it here, yes.
Krish NAik: Okay? Pretty big one, so here, actually, I passed everything, my OpenAI API key, as you can see, directly from here, my Pinecone API key.
Krish NAik: And everything in one shot. My Postgres, S3 bucket, so whatever that I am using, everything that I have passed it from here. Okay? The idea is to update that environment variables.
Krish NAik: So, I think once I have updated it, so let me just hit, enter for now.
Krish NAik: Yes, I have exposed, later on I will delete it. I need to show you this part, so this is fine.
Krish NAik: Last update in progress, the status is active, alright, fine.
Krish NAik: My phone… Alright… The function name… okay, I think I can switch on my video.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just wait.
Krish NAik: it takes some time, so just give it, close to 60 seconds, and then we'll be checking it from the eBay, because I think, I'll be getting the…
Krish NAik: Okay, okay, okay, kidding.
Krish NAik: I think I have done that wrong. No, I have not updated the function name, actually.
Krish NAik: Just wait, just wait.
Krish NAik: Okay, so CTRL-V. Here, I have to update this function name, no? I'm not using serverless anymore. Server. Okay, and with that, all my credentials, so just wait.
Krish NAik: So it will take some time, so let's wait for that to be completed.
Krish NAik: Then, once the environment variables are updated.
Krish NAik: Then we can move to the next step, so we'll just wait. So this part…
Krish NAik: your environment variables will be coming. Can you see here, once the update is done.
Krish NAik: This is my rack text to SQL, so the same thing, you guys can also see it.
Krish NAik: Please do the confirmation of this one.
Krish NAik: Still stuck on the region part, Mates. She's telling you we're stuck in the region part.
Krish NAik: Just, you have to be… confirm that in which region. So that's why, generally, with AWS Configure, it takes years of that.
Krish NAik: Yes, you can directly take all the ENV values from the, .env file.
Krish NAik: Rajat. You can take those.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I think I can pass it here.
milind kulkarni: One, quick question, Paul. I do… when I'm checking my, my function, I do see all those environment variables there, so…
milind kulkarni: Am I doing something different?
milind kulkarni: I see, like, RAT is SQL Serverless, the function name.
milind kulkarni: Right?
Krish NAik: gift.
milind kulkarni: And then I see all environment variable there, and I see the swagger also coming up, so…
Krish NAik: Alright, fine. See, actually, in my script is also, it's there, because all these environment variables are actually available in your GitHub secrets.
Krish NAik: Okay, if that TICD, in your case, if you have done it, then it will be done automatically. But right now, as I'm doing it manually, to show you, no. So that's why I've taken this one.
milind kulkarni: Okay, no problem. Thank you so much.
Krish NAik: Got it.
Krish NAik: I think just mute.
Krish NAik: lambda function name is.
Krish NAik: I think by this time the function should be active.
Krish NAik: Rack text to SQL Server, this is the name.
Krish NAik: Yes, the function is active.
Krish NAik: OPIC environment variables are updated, alright, just wait. Now, again, I will try to detect it.
Krish NAik: Because I feel if it is there, it should be there, because at least if we are reached till this step.
Krish NAik: So, things are… At least we are going in the correct direction.
Krish NAik: Alright, let me check the info.
Krish NAik: slash info, Ram is telling, at open.
Rahul: Yeah, that's…
Krish NAik: Betty Print.
Krish NAik: What's no…
Rahul: Yeah, just, slash docs, and if you hit the health endpoint, it will show you what are up and what are false.
Rahul: Docs.
Krish NAik: Let me just also shared.
Rahul: So for me, OPIC configuration is saying false, but I haven't provided the OPIC…
Rahul: keys in the environment variable. Is that the reason?
Krish NAik: Yes, if you have not provided, then how it will show…
Rahul: Your file… your file also, OPIC, is not there in the README.
Rahul: 8.
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, no, see, see, see, see, see, see, see. I have kept it there as an optional one. See, here.
Krish NAik: This one. I told you, no, see, in my deployment, I actually passed the OPIC API key here, but I kept it as an optional, because it's not necessary. So, you can add a comma here, and you can pass these three things, okay? Op stash and OPIC, those things.
Rahul: Yeah, yeah. Okay, sure.
Krish NAik: I don't know.
Krish NAik: This is optional.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Okay, Rahul… okay, Rahul only messaged. Mithesh did not change, they're working on it. Alright, Mitish, check that in your case.
Krish NAik: Okay, because even I am not sure which database I am using.
Krish NAik: Alright, so let me just, go here. I think I can reload this one.
Krish NAik: So, for example, if I check one route…
Krish NAik: Okay, so first, so Paul, because I've just started the document, let me see if something is there. Right now, zero, blank, fine.
Krish NAik: Then comes query. Directly, I can try it out, okay? So, let me make it true.
Krish NAik: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Tell me the total number of customers in the database.
Krish NAik: Let me hit it and let me see, am I getting any errors or not?
Krish NAik: Alright, customer count I'm getting is 100, so… okay, routes is working.
Krish NAik: Fine. Then comes with respect to uploading.
Krish NAik: I'm gonna try it out, choose File…
Krish NAik: I need a PDF file… okay.
Krish NAik: Download CWS, PW contract… And it is a small PDF file, small PDF, there is a small PDF file.
Krish NAik: Let's deploy that… implemented, just the data folder. Inside the data folder, I think I'll be having something.
Krish NAik: Here, with respect to the upload, okay?
Krish NAik: We'll write document.uplobe routing execute.
Krish NAik: Hmm, alright, I can see from my previous catch 8 actually picked up, so this is good, okay? I can see the catch 8 is true. Last time, I think, in the class, in the last week that I have done.
Krish NAik: Alright, now let me see, the… based on the query.
Krish NAik: Okay, so… initially, if I get the list of documents, I have my document.pdf all right.
Krish NAik: Now, coming to, query documents, let me check this out also.
Krish NAik: What is RAG?
Krish NAik: Mobilite…
Krish NAik: Okay, so based on that, RAC refers to as a rack, which are a type of this one.
Krish NAik: Okay, the sources that has been taken is from document.pdf. Okay, catch 8 is false.
Krish NAik: All right, right now. So, next time, if I try to execute, I think it should be faster, because the catch edit should be true by this end. So, yes, I can see, mainly the core functionalities I want to test. Say, okay, and I can see the app is working. To others also, please, you can provide me a confirmation on that part.
Krish NAik: Okay, and the best thing is, to look into the logs, always.
Krish NAik: Okay, so if I go into this monitor section, I think I can open my CloudWatch logs.
Krish NAik: Okay, so this is my RAG SQL Server.
Krish NAik: Why this page is not loading?
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Okay, so from here, actually, you can…
Krish NAik: I'll look into the logs for this one.
Krish NAik: Similarly, just let me open my S3.
Krish NAik: I think this is the bucket that we have been using. I uploaded a PDF file.
Krish NAik: Initially, this is my document.pdf, chunks.json, alright, this is there.
Krish NAik: Alright, so this… Partic.
Krish NAik: Working fine, I think there is no issue.
Krish NAik: Here.
Krish NAik: web app is working. Others, also, please have a try, because really, the things that I have done for right now.
Krish NAik: Connected to Pinecone, connected to Pinecone, alright, I can see here. 1, 2, connected, letters, 23 vectors, catch ahead, loaded 23 documents.
Krish NAik: This is… mind.
Krish NAik: This is a unique hash ID that has available.
Krish NAik: Alright, mmm…
Krish NAik: So, we'll pick one…
Krish NAik: documents are actually initialized. Okay, this thing looks good. Others can do the confirmation, because right now, in front of you, I have done it, guys.
Krish NAik: Because this is not till CI-CT, because the same things that will be taken care in the CICT pipeline, but this is manually I have done it. So others can also provide me the confirmation that, yes, everything is working.
Krish NAik: Fine or not.
Krish NAik: Okay, working fine. Santosh, thanks for the confirmation. Others also, please have a check, and then let me know.
Krish NAik: Because even for me, like, when I did it, I brought a lot of things, others, like HTTP, like,
Krish NAik: API gateway, also, I brought in the picture, but because of timeout issue, I removed it, actually, from the main service.
Krish NAik: First time you are doing it, it's fine. If you are doing it within 2 hours, majorly, I can say that you are in pretty much good, right? Initially, you need to understand each thing, what we are doing, so that's why, through the manual implementation, if it is working, then simply I can say that, okay, now this particular function name, I can update it directly in deploy.yml.
Krish NAik: Okay, that's the only difference.
Krish NAik: Okay, Mitesh. Alright, great you for bigger tattoo.
Krish NAik: Always just be sure a single workflow you are using. It means that the same terminal, same everything is better.
Krish NAik: Sometimes. Balaji is telling in CICD pipeline it failed at update lambda function because it was not created. From then on, I will go with the manual route and see everything is working, is my understanding? Yes. See, Balaji. First, I did everything manual. Later on, if you have the function already available, then automatically that pipeline will be executed.
Krish NAik: Because that's why I showed you step-by-step.
Krish NAik: Okay, creating the function, then providing the permissions, updating the environment variables, and tested also. Now, if you are using the same Lambda function, which is already created, then there won't be any type of issue.
Krish NAik: Yes, I rejected.
Krish NAik: Nawabi? Yes, tech.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, so, can I share, one issue?
Krish NAik: Okay, you are in panelist only, so you can share.
Rajat Khanna: Susie.
Krish NAik: Yes, now are we, what you were telling, you have written iPod.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Rajat Khanna: So here, I have uploaded a PDF file.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, so it, firstly, it takes time, then it got uploaded. But then, if I, have, the file name or something, I ask, so here, the file name is the other file that I uploaded, from local, I bought testing, so those things. I have not uploaded this one. If I try to change the query, it is not, asking on behalf of this file.
Rajat Khanna: It is asking on behalf of the older, previously available file. Why that is happening?
Krish NAik: Share your screen, share your screen.
Rajat Khanna: I'm cheating.
Krish NAik: App is working, now it's nothing related to deployment.
Krish NAik: It is related to, probably, in your vector databases. Previously, vectors were there. Based on that, it can work. Okay, but are you getting the response? That is the main thing that I'm looking for.
Rajat Khanna: So, no, I… so, the first question that also came to my mind, so if I uploaded a new file, and then if I check, if I want to check the question on the older file that is available, so how to do those things?
Krish NAik: It will work now automatically. For your older files, the channels are available in your P2DB, so it doesn't matter. From there only, it will pick up.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, so now, if I have uploaded a resume file of this PDF one, and from the query, if I ask…
Rajat Khanna: What is the name?
Rajat Khanna: And click on execute. So, it will search on both the files, that were available.
Rajat Khanna: So, see, the certificate, IDR, and… it's…
Krish NAik: C.
Rajat Khanna: note.
Krish NAik: Your vector database is saying how many documents you post, you can ask any question from any documents.
Rajat Khanna: But why that, so it's only showing 3 files, the latest one is not coming here.
Krish NAik: Latest one is not coming here. Share your screen, show me. Okay, I think you are already sharing, yes.
Krish NAik: The latest one is not coming here.
Rajat Khanna: Hmm.
Rajat Khanna: I have uploaded this one.
Rajat Khanna: this.
Krish NAik: Right now, you have uploaded.
Krish NAik: Because, actually, I think that if it is going inside slash temp, or… just check in your S3, it's going or not.
Rajat Khanna: S3…
Krish NAik: All right now, Abhi, I can see your knobs.
Krish NAik: When I tried to clear the GitHub disk space, it fixed the automated flow you gave with following. I added it to the top of your deployment file. Okay, just wait. I will ask you to share the screen and share the same info if somebody is facing that particular issue.
Rajat Khanna: Where I can see the file name, it is showing…
Krish NAik: by default, like, everything will be coming as document.pdfm only.
Krish NAik: Because this is right now February 1.
Krish NAik: According to your time, when I see.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, so see, all… so yeh rahat ki, upload zah. Abhi Jomani ki au niwa.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Just wait, because let me just check, that particular configuration once.
Krish NAik: Just wait.
Krish NAik: probably that is where you were saving, I need to look into that particular configuration.
Krish NAik: It's going into… temp directory… Not damp, alright.
Krish NAik: Because I think that I'll be updating it during the CIC night.
Krish NAik: this part, I have not kept it, directly, in this one.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Because, yes, I don't think I have kept it in this part. If I even look into the environment variables with respect to S3… Alright, and even let me just, check your code, that in your code, when you have deployed, and that, local one, so you can check the health route. Check the health route only.
Rajat Khanna: So you'd seen, the, lambda.
Rajat Khanna: environment.
Krish NAik: Okay, okay, this is fine, just scroll down, scroll down, scroll down, scroll down.
Krish NAik: Virtue S3…
Krish NAik: I think it is inside the info route of which route that SK is getting used, or that local is getting used.
Krish NAik: Just, that part I need to confirm just for it. I think it will be there.
Krish NAik: Inside, your, info router.
Rajat Khanna: It's going local, no? See?
Krish NAik: See, then you have to change it in the port, no? In your local… if it is there, then how it will do.
Krish NAik: Just waiting, when I am at…
Rajat Khanna: changed anything, means, last night I was also facing same, it was always going to local, but I have copy-pasted it, so in the app, and config, so… Just wait.
Krish NAik: just wait. I will check your local, that exactly the code that, you have, like, during the Docker build. If in the code it's local, then it won't go to S3.
Krish NAik: Dark Slay.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just create.
Krish NAik: activate both.
Krish NAik: Because I think in some route I kept that, that's why I'm checking exactly, like, in which route I kept at.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright. Now, check your local, wherever it's there. Backend is S3.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah.
Krish NAik: Okay? And, check your ENV file also.
Krish NAik: If, somewhere that, particular variable. Because it has to be.
Rajat Khanna: This is the code which is deployed, currently, so there is no ENV file here, no?
Krish NAik: Okay, alright. Because, from your Docker build, I think I have not picked up. So, if it is there, this data slash, upload, this has to be only with your local prospect.
Krish NAik: If it is there, then I think self.storage, I've defined this. Okay, return slash temp slash, okay, now this is fine, slash temp slash
Krish NAik: Catch it, now this is fine. Now the bucket is… that you are using,
Krish NAik: Scroll below, the name of the bucket is here only.
Krish NAik: In config.py. Rag catcher bucket. Okay? This is the name of the bucket that you have. Alright, and then, I think… Okay, now go back to AWS, then show me that part.
Krish NAik: My rat catch bucket, Rajat123.
Krish NAik: Okay… now, why the name of the bucket got changed?
Rajat Khanna: I have given…
Krish NAik: do same things, man. If you try to change something, it even becomes… in GitHub Secrets, what you have kept it. In code, what you have kept it. In deploy.yml.you have kept it, anything, just keep it sane. If you keep changing names.
Rajat Khanna: Oh, no, no.
Krish NAik: That's very hard.
Rajat Khanna: Everything I have just kept the same if, this is the old file, and here… so if you see, I have just given all the environments which is available here.
Krish NAik: Okay, now this is your new one.
Rajat Khanna: This is the old one, which has the ENV file and everything, so from there.
Krish NAik: Okay, okay.
Rajat Khanna: We'll be based.
Krish NAik: So, for the new one, just maintain that bucket name, then.
Krish NAik: So, because, see, here I can see rack catcher bucket is there. That's why I'm getting confused.
Rajat Khanna: Oh, okay.
Rajat Khanna: We are done, huh?
Krish NAik: You have to use the same one everywhere. If you keep on changing, like, it becomes harder for me to debug also.
Krish NAik: Alright, it's telling fail to query the documents rack by plane, fail to generate an embeddings connection error. It has to be, like, probably check your logs, Rishi. From logs only you can get it.
Krish NAik: Okay, and I think, Nawavi, just raise your hand, Nawavi, that, thing that you told, I think it might be helpful for… you need to clear the GitHub Actions, that page.
Krish NAik: Okay, so now, where are you? You can simply tell that.
Krish NAik: Okay, yes. Allowed to talk. Okay, and I will add you to panelist, because this might be helpful to Rajas, because your GitHub space, if it's getting full, then because of that, you might get an issue.
Nawavi: Hello, Paul, can you hear me?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, I can.
Nawavi: Paul, like, I was struggling with the same issue, the one… a few of them are like us, like, with the, failing the automated workflow.
Nawavi: So, when I tried it, like, with clearing the, when I checked the error message, it showed… do you… do you want me to show the… show my screen?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes, you can share your screen, you are in the.
Nawavi: Oh, goodness.
Krish NAik: Rajat, check this part, because he actually cleared out, all the things from, like, GitHub disk.
Krish NAik: If the GitHub disk is full, then you will face that issue.
Nawavi: Give me a minute.
Krish NAik: Okay, Rishi, don't worry, I will look into that, Rishi.
Nawavi: I have some issues in sharing the screen. I'll just mute, like…
Krish NAik: I think, first time, are you sharing?
Nawavi: Yes. Yeah.
Krish NAik: No? Okay.
Krish NAik: If you're in Mac, those pop-ups come, generally.
Nawavi: Yes, yes, that's the permissions, like I said.
Krish NAik: Can you finish it.
Nawavi: Yeah, just a minute.
Nawavi: So, basically, I had the same issue. The one… one of the, participants showed, like, having, like, a segmented,
Nawavi: disk images in the, AWS.
Krish NAik: He is.
Nawavi: You don't see it yet, right?
Krish NAik: No.
Nawavi: Do you see my screen? No, right?
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no.
Krish NAik: Currently.
Krish NAik: So, Rahul, just wait, because I know in my, Docker build, I've kept libcx.
Krish NAik: All this, installations, actually.
Rahul: Okay.
Rahul: Yeah, my… everything is working, but when logs are saying something and my… My health and point,
Rahul: When I'm trying to upload the document, it says internal server error.
Rahul: But the same document, I'm able to see it in S3.
Krish NAik: Alright, because there can be some issue with respect to docklink. Because your PDF is getting uploaded, that is fine, that is not related to chunking, but after that, docklink is related to that chunking, but probably in chunking, it is failing.
Krish NAik: This leaves CX, okay, because of, that dependency. Just wait, because I knew that in my Dockerfile, I have kept the installation of that.
Krish NAik: Using DNF install command.
Rahul: Basically, it's not parsing the right, context.
Rahul: And…
Krish NAik: In chunking, it is the issue. I know. Correct. It is the docklink hybrid chunker that might be creating the issue.
Krish NAik: Just wait. First of all, now we… yes, now we can see your screen. So, like, people who are getting that error that in your GitHub actions, that automatically is getting stopped, like Rajat was facing, okay, in that particular case.
Krish NAik: Now we can go back to your deploy.main file.
Nawavi: Sure. So, it was the same issue, like, the one… one of the, partsmen asked me, Paul, like, I had this kind of segmented, like, disk before, these ones, the earlier ones, as you can see in the date.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Nawavi: to, to fix it, what I… so, when I tried in GitHub Actions, it was stuck for, like, hours before, like, this time when I tried this, it took about 40 minutes, like, as you can see. It runs, like, up to the, the place where it was stuck before with the pushing the image.
Nawavi: So, to fix it, what I tried is this.
Nawavi: In India.
Krish NAik: When your screen sharing stopped.
Nawavi: Yeah, in the, in the…
Krish NAik: Alright. I can see you now, right?
Nawavi: So, sick.
Krish NAik: Okay, you know what, but… Added free dig space, that part, okay, alright.
Nawavi: It just, just so…
Krish NAik: I'll need to put this part.
Nawavi: Paul, like, I added this part on top of your CDCID file.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright. In that you have added that, first clear the text place in GitHub, and then only start the main deployment part.
Nawavi: I think since it's, like, a 5GB, like, I had the previous, like, projects as well, maybe I… my… I don't know, it's something unique to me, but it fixed that issue, the one… one of the participants, that's what I wanted to tell you.
Krish NAik: Alright. So, like, take the copy of this entire deploy.yml file and create a gest.
Krish NAik: Take a public list and share, I think that will be better.
Nawavi: Abil, Abil. Thanks a lot. I really like your work, and thanks, thanks for everything, Paul. I follow your work.
Krish NAik: Alright, that's great. So now, coming to Rao's issue. Rahul's issue, because in Dockerfile, I've specifically written to install that lib.
Krish NAik: See, all those little things I have written in Dockerfile, okay? So, let me check in Dockerfile once.
Rahul: Yeah, if you see the logs, it says what's happening is…
Krish NAik: dock link conversion failed to pass. Got that. Because of that, it could not, keep it clear.
Krish NAik: Okay, because this is a dockling issue that I am facing here, I'm making…
Krish NAik: Just to wait, okay, I will try to upload a PDF. Let me see if I am facing that same issue.
Rahul: Yeah, yeah. Just try it, because it says the document file is uploaded.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, but the chunking, is failing.
Rahul: Exactly, exactly.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes.
Rahul: Looking at the…
Krish NAik: Got the issue, got the issue. Because of this issue only, I moved to X86764, because of this chunking.
Rahul: Oh, okay, okay.
Krish NAik: In ARM64, PyTorch was creating the issue because of, link. Just wait, let me check by passing something else. Where is the upload route, upload, upload, just wait. This is upload route, alright.
Krish NAik: You're gonna choose a fight.
Krish NAik: Alright, these are the two documents, leave these two documents. I will upload, something fresh, and I think this one. Latency, why it matters, where rack performance breakdown.
Krish NAik: This is a complex PDF, actually. Fine, I can upload anything for now.
Krish NAik: Let me see whether my dockling is failing or not. If my dockling is failing, it means that there is some issue.
Krish NAik: In my setup, also.
Rahul: Yeah, this takes a long time, so if you go back… Oh, this is…
Krish NAik: fine.
Rahul: In the… in the logs, it will show you in the Lambda logs.
Krish NAik: I'll read, I'll read, huh, just read.
Krish NAik: Those lambda logs.
Rahul: the document has come in, how to reduce rgilatency.pdf, so that's coming through parsing and chunking document with context awareness.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine, I think, because of that, it's waiting otherwise.
Krish NAik: Just wait, let me see, like, what is the response that I get here.
Krish NAik: Just sweet.
Rahul: Second last name.
Krish NAik: It looks like that, the libx over. Actually, it's nothing, then I will add that particular specific package in Dockerfile. I've already kept all the lib ones. The CHC meat got missed, it looks like.
Krish NAik: Yeah, so it should not take so much time, because the error will be same for him, and we just wrote.
Krish NAik: Let me check the logs again.
Krish NAik: Then now it got stuck, finally it will throw an error at the…
Rahul: Correct. After this, it will throw an error here. For me, it took the same amount of time
Rahul: I was a pleasure.
Krish NAik: running in my Dockerfile, I need to update this one.
Krish NAik: Cesaro.
Krish NAik: this one.
Krish NAik: Error failed, this is coming because of docklink.
Krish NAik: And the installation is this particular package.
Krish NAik: Okay, now this particular package… Let me go to my docker, docker, docker file, docker.lambda…
Krish NAik: Majorly with respect to GCC Allow it, okay?
Krish NAik: Because here… can you see all the list of, like, these I have installed for Docklink?
Krish NAik: Okay, now this is XCB exactly, which is the name of the package, let me check.
Krish NAik: LiveXCV1… Alright, I will just go ahead and… Ctrl-F… Okay, this is missing.
Rahul: Connect.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine.
Krish NAik: Let me just add it to you.
Krish NAik: Under all the links.
Rahul: now re-push.
Rajat Khanna: space, space, issue, which file I need to update?
Krish NAik: I think,
Krish NAik: Now, I'll be… please share that guest, and you need to update your deploy.by, just wait. Once you share the guest, I will share it with you.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Rajat Khanna: Now, I got that error in the GitHub. After changing the S3 bucket list name, I pushed the code.
Rajat Khanna: Now in.
Krish NAik: moderate.
Rajat Khanna: Knowing that error.
Krish NAik: Now, in the git, it's showing the error. In git, what is the error?
Rajat Khanna: So, error mount, callback failure, and then it is showing failed to write, compress, fail to create different streams, so…
Krish NAik: Just wait, your error is different, I will look into that.
Krish NAik: Just wait, this is my Lambda function server this time. ECR repository is also server, I think.
Krish NAik: Just wait, let me do the build again for the docker. One, let me push docker file update.
Krish NAik: Query, update.
Krish NAik: Yeah, lambda, let me just write it down. Yes.
Rajat Khanna: No, you're me.
Krish NAik: I think I can comment.
Krish NAik: Just gonna chat.
Krish NAik: I hope the package is, like, let me also check it in GPT once, because I'm installing it in this one, so DNF install is the alternate or not.
Krish NAik: Because you just need to add that package. If the package is missing because of that, I think it will create the issue.
Rahul: Oh, it's in… it's in, dockerfile.lambda, right?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, this is correct.
Rahul: So, rebuild the image, push it… push the change again.
Krish NAik: Okay, if you need riders for compiling the stuff…
Krish NAik: That is giving me two package, Davy and Bash. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, again, I have to do that. It's telling the DNF install libxcb. Let me check libxcb is here in my, Docker file.
Krish NAik: dockerfile.lambda… LiveXC is actually there.
Krish NAik: And this is…
Rahul: Let's XCB1.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Rahul: The difference between 1 and CV?
Krish NAik: It is for APT.
Krish NAik: Like, for Ubuntu, generally, it is used, but not in DNF.
Krish NAik: That's why. So, you know, some app is failing, telling me which one it was seen, just wait.
Krish NAik: very specific limit to all… LibXCB, this is the package it's telling to do the installation.
Krish NAik: Verify the associ… Dnfx11, actually…
Krish NAik: All the package which this is suggesting, I have added it.
Krish NAik: Mesa, live, mesa, okay, this also, I have added it.
Krish NAik: Jeez.
Krish NAik: Does it blow around… Then the lambda of 5, where is the lambda lambda?
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Or dorky and dietitian.
Krish NAik: Because the base image of lambda, if I try to change that.
Krish NAik: Because working with Ubuntu is always safer, rather than working with the DNF package manager. Because DNF is based on Amazon, Linux, and RHEL, and Fedora.
Krish NAik: That's why this package…
Krish NAik: Alright, that's why I do have a flag in my code also, just wait.
Krish NAik: In my code.
Krish NAik: In, configCC, where is my config? Under app? Config.print why?
Krish NAik: Yes, lambda, okay, this part is correct, no shows.
Krish NAik: Okay, and now this Boolean is true.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, generally, like, I can set it to false.
Krish NAik: That is, other way around, because in my code, I have a backup of unstructured also. Okay, but, let me see, because I think the installation will fail. The name of the package is different, so just read. Yes, I think because of the name of the package, it's failing.
Krish NAik: build and tag, yes, so there is no such package called as the LibXC1 that I've told you.
Krish NAik: Hmm… Alright, fine, like, if I make my… Condition as false right now.
Krish NAik: Then comes… D… Docker, the lambda file… Added under LeadChave 1.
Rahul: Boole in your config.wypi, use docklin boolean as false for AMD64 to avoid PyTorch and Unix error.
Krish NAik: Yes, that is for, actually, because the fallback is with unstructured. So, let me see that whether unstructured can do that or not.
Krish NAik: That's why I kept the fallback tool in that reason.
Krish NAik: Let me see in this place.
Krish NAik: Because that is the main, thing, like, if I'm working with Lambda, I need an Amazon Linux image only.
Krish NAik: And in that image, like, this is the main one.
Krish NAik: In DocLink, for PDF support, you need Cairo, and Cairo needs support of XCV, that Lib XCV package.
Krish NAik: Okay, so multi yet. Right now, the document I am uploading is PDF, so it's hitting Cairo, and Cairo will hit your XCV.
Krish NAik: Because of that, and even with…
Krish NAik: So, let me just see that part.
Krish NAik: Because the other way around, is like adding a layer. How many of you know lambda layers?
Krish NAik: Manually, I can add lambda layers also. Okay, so I think, thanks for sharing the guest, just wait.
Krish NAik: I think, this is a question, Rajat, for you.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you can look into this deploy.yml file. Initially, he has added only these lines. From line number, I think, from this part, free disk space, line number 21, till 30.
Krish NAik: For clearing your GitHub disk space.
Krish NAik: Okay, so I've shared it in the chat. Raja, this is for you.
Krish NAik: Yes, that's why, because manually I can add a layer of docklink, but, let me see. So that's why I will just have a look, and then, finally, let me check on that.
Krish NAik: Because there are so many workarounds.
Krish NAik: But, lately.
Rajat Khanna: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Now, as I'm working with container images, no, so in container images, you cannot actually add lambda layers.
Krish NAik: Delta… Other way around.
Krish NAik: So, probably I need to change something.
Krish NAik: and change docklink, and I can use a simple library, but just because of docklink, this issue is coming.
Krish NAik: So, let me see if the fallback strategy works or not.
Rajat Khanna: Oh, pretty,
Rajat Khanna: A poll, that, free disk space, showed an error, please complete the exit code 2.
Krish NAik: Even I have not tested that in my system, so really, I'm not sure.
Rajat Khanna: I told the solution interviewer.
Rajat Khanna: I'll share my screen.
Rajat Khanna: So… Just… Show you.
Rajat Khanna: So, I have added these lines only.
Rajat Khanna: And… after that, so it showed this error.
Rajat Khanna: Are you looking into, my screen sharing?
Krish NAik: I'm looking into my deployment. Because, yeah, your part, even not, I have tested, so really, now we can look into,
Krish NAik: to your one, okay? Now we just have a look at… show the deploy.yml. If there is something with respect to your deploy.yml file, then only
Krish NAik: Free disk is part only. Just check that all those indentations and everything is correct.
Rajat Khanna: Only this part I have added.
Krish NAik: Yes, this is fine, line number… 10 to 20, while applying…
Krish NAik: Yes, JSON I have not, tested, really. I've done the test with TXT and PDF only, but I think JSON parsing is there, as a fallback.
Krish NAik: Okay, so just wait.
Krish NAik: let me first see that at least PDFs are getting uploaded, then that is with respect to your core application. In your local, when you run it, Santosh, first of all, check any local also, once that support is there with respect to JSON.
Krish NAik: Because event handler talking version…
Krish NAik: Popular Cairo. Okay, let me check, do I have Cairo or not?
Krish NAik: Because of Cairo also, I can get that one DNF install.
Krish NAik: Alright, remove, catch a DNF. Okay, so… DDL docklings…
Krish NAik: Fight Habib.
Krish NAik: Taking that one… No cache directory, pip.
Krish NAik: My image is also getting built, so once I do that, let me see the fallback with respect to unstructured is working or not.
Krish NAik: All right, fine, I will do a complete revision in the next class, TJ, don't worry.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Because some things, then from Sunday, we will start with the next project.
Krish NAik: And there is no west.
Krish NAik: Because I know this deployment even, like, I worked more than 6 hours on this one. I've changed the architecture also. This is fine. No issues, but the core application is up, so I can say more than 50% things are done. Only now, with respect to data routes, we need to have a check.
Krish NAik: Okay, so don't worry, people.
Krish NAik: But at least, like, for most of you, the swag rev is up, so that is the first one.
Krish NAik: Because when I check all the system dependencies.
Krish NAik: The piece lambda image is 3.11, alright.
Krish NAik: other dependencies.
Rahul: Yeah, I'm also encountering the same issue.
Rahul: Line number 9… Which one?
Rahul: Yeah, but the one you are seeing it.
Krish NAik: Hmm.
Rahul: So, deployment.yml at line number 9.
Rahul: I don't.
Krish NAik: I have not tested it. Rajat, I think, now I'll be told smoking, now I'll be there where?
Krish NAik: Are you unmoted, or whether he, like.
Rahul: We see a repository, should we…
Krish NAik: Now, are you here only, okay? I'm allowing to talk, you can.
Krish NAik: Check that button.
Krish NAik: Because I'm fixing another issue right now.
Rajat Khanna: So, I'm, sharing my screen, so I think there is some coma that needs to be there.
Nawavi: Hey, Rajal, give me a minute, like, you can hear me, right?
Rajat Khanna: I'm sharing my screen, so I am not able to see any other, screen button.
Nawavi: I just copied those, like, a place, only 10 lines to the original file, just to make sure it is the same, because I… give me a minute, I'll get back to you, give me one minute.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Alright, I got the problem. I got the problem.
Rajat Khanna: Oh, my… That's basically…
Krish NAik: See.
Rajat Khanna: Light number 21.
Nawavi: Yeah.
Krish NAik: Okay, I think I got the problem. Yes, Cairo and two other packages were there. Tango and Harabas was missing, okay? So, let me update my Docker file and redo the push.
Krish NAik: Okay, that was the main con of one, that's why…
Nawavi: Sorry, Paul, I missed that part.
Krish NAik: No, no, not for you, for Rahul and for others also. This is a Dockerfile change, docker.lambda.file, like, two packages were missing, Cairo and Tango. Okay, so because of that, we were facing that particular issue.
Krish NAik: I think run DNA, PDF core rendering. Okay, I'm updating that file, and I'm pushing it just here.
Krish NAik: Because my new deployment…
Krish NAik: I will start with the new push shoe.
Krish NAik: Dockerfile update, okay, so this is fine.
Krish NAik: DNF install, this is yours.
Krish NAik: verify updates.
Krish NAik: Because exactly, in Docker, I'm toppling the issue was there.
Krish NAik: Because the docklink stack is a really big one, so from GitHub.
Krish NAik: Now I will start sharing my… Spring queueso.
Krish NAik: I think which one? No, no, this green, I think the other one. This is the text of 3S.
Krish NAik: So here, I have added this package, Cairo Pango Free Type Hair Buzz. Okay, now these were for Docklink stock, very specifically. Okay, so because of this, that issue was there. So let me now check my deployment. I think this will automatically pause.
Krish NAik: Let me go to my Text2SQL, yes.
Krish NAik: The new one.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: Alrighty, guys, wait a bit, because I think that will fix the issue. Okay, so you can also, check. I have added, actually, I think, 5 packages in my, Docker file. So if I show you in GitHub,
Krish NAik: Okay, so this was a guest from him, I think.
Krish NAik: Docker, docker, Docker, where is my docker.yamda is?
Krish NAik: So here, I have added… okay, now these packages, actually. This, was missing in my case, so I have added it.
Krish NAik: Okay, Cairo.
Krish NAik: I think, I can know, okay. Alright, I think I have not updated the variable also.
Krish NAik: I'm talking.
Krish NAik: Let me make it too far.
Krish NAik: Okay, so you can look into my GitHub, and you can just take those
Krish NAik: I can say these packages in line number 9… from 98 till 102. Okay, these 5 packages that needs to be added. You can take a git pull, or anything that you can do from your end.
Rajat Khanna: Oh, no.
Krish NAik: We'll just wait for the final push, and hope that it will…
Krish NAik: For dockling error, guys, I've fixed that particular issue.
Krish NAik: Okay, so please have a check on that.
Krish NAik: And try to make a new bid in your CI.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, can I share my screen?
Krish NAik: Yes, eventually yes, please.
Krish NAik: But…
Rajat Khanna: Okay,
Rajat Khanna: So, just to, give you reference what changes is done, I have not, till post, pushed these changes that you have pasted.
Rajat Khanna: But in the deploy.yml, so, the free disk space, so this comma needs to be there. So, after pushing this,
Rajat Khanna: comma for this commented out, so now this is, at here. If it fail from here, then I'll push, the new changes, from this.
Krish NAik: Perfect.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, and in the local one, so as, you told, so the, this S3 bucket name was not same. So, I have, done this build, and I have pushed, tagged the image, and I have just pushed one, the latest one, right now.
Rajat Khanna: waiting for this. If that… this gets completed, then I think…
Rajat Khanna: It will not be needed to do anything further.
Rajat Khanna: For you, I think you are more comfortable in command line, but I think if we do it from the web application aspects, so it will be more easier to understand.
Krish NAik: It's not easy, they are also, like, whichever way, because both the thing works. EY… like, later on, the plan was I will create a bash script. So, using that script, everything that I can automate in one shot.
Krish NAik: Whereas automation cannot be done through UI, that's fine.
Rajat Khanna: Automation, as in?
Krish NAik: this entire script, like, command-wise you have executed, I will create a single BAS script, and in that script, everything will be done in one shot.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Krish NAik: That was the main purpose.
Nawavi: Hey, Rajit,
Nawavi: I think this step is only needed for me first time, because, like, I think I… maybe from other projects, I had this space kind of filled.
Nawavi: After that, I think if you just… if it is working, just if you comment, and if you run that part, the flow would run faster, but the first time, it took more than about 30 minutes for me. After that, it was fine. Like, I don't know it will work for you guys, but just… I just mentioned. Sorry about that quote, okay?
Rajat Khanna: No issues, no issues. Now that, DT space, worked for me, so hopefully, this error will also
Rajat Khanna: Because previously it shows the same, if I show you my… This…
Rajat Khanna: chat, and it also this one. So I got this error.
Rajat Khanna: I see.
Rajat Khanna: So, it's both the same solution that you pasted.
Nawavi: Thanks. Thanks, Bob.
Krish NAik: Alright, Santosh, I will, look into that one. Just wait.
Krish NAik: First, at least, the PDF part is done, then I will move to that.
Krish NAik: Because in my case, the build is done. Right now, finally, I think, uploading the image in ECR.
Krish NAik: Okay, so let me start sharing my screen.
Krish NAik: Hmm…
Rahul: Yum.
Rahul: It's going for me, too, in parallel, yeah.
Krish NAik: But really, I don't know the size of Cairo Penguin, these things.
Krish NAik: Dark swine.
Rahul: How did you find that, Paul? Like, that those packages are required for docking?
Krish NAik: two or three GitHub issues in docking that I got.
Rahul: Okay.
Krish NAik: Because, majorly, like, they were also trying to use Dockling, only Dockling in Lambda.
Krish NAik: Okay, now those… there it was mentioned. So let me see that whether it works, because something is written in GitHub, which is even I cannot say it's a foolproof.
Rahul: Yeah.
Krish NAik: solution. Only people do thumbs up.
Krish NAik: That's why. Two thumbs up, I saw. Based on that, I added it. Let me see.
Krish NAik: Because the flow in Dockling is such a way, first, Dockling will call Cairo, and Cairo will call Lib CNC. So, I think in our case that Cairo was missing, that might be creating that issue.
Rahul: Yeah.
Rahul: My image is pushed, so I'm going…
Krish NAik: million. People who want to drop, you can drop, okay? Like, it's fine. Like, next class, again, the same thing, I will do a complete revision. I will test all those things.
Krish NAik: Because, but I hope, like, more than 50-60% you guys have done it, only now related to the poor functionalities, that is the main part. Okay, so yes, if you want to…
milind kulkarni: Wouldn't…
milind kulkarni: One quick, should we… should we… I'm just checking from cost point of view, I don't mind keeping it there.
milind kulkarni: Will it be… will it cost too much if I keep the stuff there? I can delete and recreate, and I'm confident about that.
Krish NAik: This is serverless.
milind kulkarni: If nobody's using it, why will we be getting charged?
milind kulkarni: Okay, no worries. I will… I will just keep watching, and it is too much. I'm going to work tomorrow, so I'll see you tomorrow again. No problem. Thanks, folks.
Krish NAik: Okay, they are cheap. Charges come just because of storage part. In the FRL storage, I mentioned at 10GB for that charge will be there, but that is very less charge.
Krish NAik: That's a problem.
Krish NAik: Otherwise, the main thing is, if you're deleting it in the next class, just before the class, just be sure, 30 minutes, you just create the lambda function. That is, only those 3 things are required.
Krish NAik: Other than that, you won't need to delete anything, yes.
milind kulkarni: No problem. Thanks. Thank you.
Krish NAik: So, Paul, I joined…
Rahul: I'm enrolled into that project thing also, so there are two points that I wanted to…
Krish NAik: Highlight here. Yes, I think at night, Chris fired me.
Krish NAik: After the session, because I was having the session, I think, in UDS, no? My session is blocked and that, so my timing, so I could not go there.
Krish NAik: So, Alexa, Krish called me, and, like, we were having a discussion. Then I came to know that he also joined. I think Jatindar was there, Balaji was there. Later on, I looked into the recording, that's it.
Rahul: So, Paul, my question is, see, this multi-source, this whole exercise.
Rahul: people in US also are doing it, and it's pretty expensive.
Rahul: So, second, you know, the point that I'm trying to do is…
Rahul: See, this backend system, how are you going to plug this with
Rahul: With, a use case, a business use case.
Rahul: which is trying to say I'm working in an insurance company.
Rahul: an insurance company, there are a lot of use cases or PDF that has to be uploaded, and then the derived use cases, because
Rahul: we are migrating systems, complex systems, from mainframes to AWS. You know, that's the use, okay? Then the second is.
Rahul: if those… if those PDFs and if those, user policies are getting uploaded and
Rahul: further divided into different, automation use cases that the function or the transactional mainframes, COBOL mainframe code are getting migrated to, say, AWS infrastructure. That has to be tested with Apple to Apple, like, each of the use cases.
Rahul: My requirement… is, like, attached to SQL API.
Rahul: This could serve me to upload those larger set of documents and define those use cases to effectively pass to the, to the integration test, or to the automation use cases test in the Lambda function itself, you know.
Rahul: So my point is, connecting… Connecting to…
Rahul: VANA, or connecting to Open Source Radesh, or connecting to Super Database, connecting to…
Rahul: So many different things will not be practically allowed, you know, in the restricted informational area, right?
Rahul: So, all that…
Krish NAik: My priest.
Rahul: It needs to be changed to something which is more in-house.
Krish NAik: Yes. Like, see, for example, if you're telling that you were working with AWS Infra, then use everything from AWS.
Krish NAik: That's the main thing, no? That's why I shared, I think, even one document. It means the solution that I have built, here I have used multiple types of things, but for a specific service, if I'm looking for cloud-specific with AWS, every service like AWS has it. For OCR, other things, everything.
Krish NAik: You can use all those services related to AWS.
Rahul: Okay, so what you're saying, the RAG, you're talking about AWS rag info.md file that you shared, right?
Krish NAik: GJCSS, that list I shared, no?
Rahul: Okay.
Rahul: So, the same configuration, the same set of thing, I can change it.
Rahul: To configure everything for, say, for example, Titan, you know, Amazon Titan, I can use it for embedding, you know?
Krish NAik: Yes. Even, like, AWS has a marketplace also. So, for example, if you're working with any other things, okay, that integration can also be done. So, everything will be through AWS infra only.
Krish NAik: you don't need to get out of the AWS interval. If something third-party comes also into the picture, AWS has majorly all these systems that I feel in the marketplace available. So those integrations, like, I think Voyage AI is, they are majorly all the
Krish NAik: good emitting models, LLM, everything is available. So you can use completely AWS N4, you don't need to move anywhere. Redis is already available. So probably, with respect to the vector TV, you can keep your vector TV in S3, and you can use OpenSearch with that. That's, like, two services that need to…
Krish NAik: combined, rather than right here in a single vector, DB can do everything. So in that way, little bit of tweaks that you need to do.
Rahul: So, for example, AWS Lambda, when we are trying to execute a chunking algorithm, you know, it… your document says that the function could have semantic, recursive, fixed, and sentence, like, but it doesn't say,
Rahul: which, like, for here, we are, example, using Dockling, for example, you know?
Rahul: So, in AWS system, which,
Rahul: which chunking, algorithm should I be using, and where is the code? What is the…
Krish NAik: See, now, AWS doesn't have… I don't think they have a charging directly, AWS has it. Okay, like, using some library only, open source, that you need to do that particular integration. It can be based on docklings, or so many options are there.
Krish NAik: Okay, like, Chonky is also there. Docklings, I feel that it's good.
Krish NAik: Because in your, like, as you told, you have those insurance-based documents. I don't think it will be only text, but it will be tables and other things.
Krish NAik: Okay, so now, for those, Dockling is really good, like, Dockling with granite support.
Krish NAik: IBM has that granite support, so there, it's actually for cables and other things, table farmers.
Krish NAik: through that, you can read. So, I feel that talking will be good as compared to others, if you need that multimodal support also.
Rahul: Yeah, what I was proposing, Paul, to Chris was, rather playing a game of
Rahul: quantitative… quantity versus qualitative, you know, difference. If there are 6… Even 10 number, or 50…
Rahul: Number of people which are moving from intermediate to advanced level.
Rahul: And in advance, they are having very specific, you know, challenges and… their own… use cases.
Rahul: And the way the US works is they don't care, like, how many projects you have explored and done.
Rahul: What they care is, how many failures have you noticed?
Rahul: And what… how did you debug those failures and then came up with a solution, you know?
Rahul: So…
Krish NAik: Alright.
Rahul: I think so. The point that is getting missed is,
Rahul: If you charge higher amount for an advanced user, And conduct only in advance?
Rahul: a core concept, project-by-project basis, then the discussion becomes entirely different, right? Then the people will be… here, people will be willing to pay that money if someone at the same caliber level comes up, and then…
Rahul: we can show, these are the real-time project challenges, let's solve one problem at a time. And that could be…
Rahul: That could be… you know… Many such problems, you know, like… for example.
Krish NAik: I got your thing. Even last… I remember last night also you pulled the same thing. That's the thing, see, we have to do that experiment.
Krish NAik: Okay, and who is willing to take that up? Because I know… because with respect to R&D, I'm the only guy.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, if I take that up, because, see, I'm planning to take an advance, I have no issues.
Krish NAik: Okay, but, the main thing is that when I look at… I always look at at least the number of students. Okay, that will be coming, because I don't prefer only 20-30 students, because when I feel that at least I feel that close to, like, 100, 150 students should be there.
Krish NAik: Okay, now the question comes, because when we do the experiment, just think, if I launch a batch, okay, generally what happens, I launch the batch just at a certain amount.
Krish NAik: Okay, or something like 50K. Previously, we have seen that
Krish NAik: only 10 students came. That is a major problem. 20 students came.
Krish NAik: Now, neither I can close the batch, it means that I'm stuck for 6 months.
Krish NAik: That becomes one problem. So, like most of the other, we try to play a little bit much more safer. Okay, so rather than going to very niche, try to keep it much more generic, okay, so that a wider audience can… I can get your point.
Rahul: increase the… increase the cost of the training to a certain level that I have a benchmark of, say, I would like to generate 10 lakh rupee
Rahul: whether it comes with 10 people, or 20 people, or 50 people, the number should not matter, right? The cost of…
Rahul: The effort versus the quality of…
Krish NAik: The thing that you were telling, no, we do it, for that one, like, when we do corporate trainings, like, only we go for, like, 7 to 10 days, but again, the thing that I deliver there for 7 days, if I'm going for 8 hours also, even I don't feel that
Krish NAik: Like, I've delivered a lot, though. Like, there are only, like, 20 developers are there, like, more than 5 years of experience.
Krish NAik: And based on their requirement, I have to, like, work on that particular content. Okay, I got your point. Simply, like, based on that, okay, I can do the experiment, like, once this batch gets completed, okay?
Krish NAik: then probably in this batch, let me take… then I needed at least an estimated number, like, how many students can come. Before that, let's finalize some amount of curriculum, 50% I will put from my side.
Krish NAik: 50%, let's do discussion, like, at least 5 to 6 rounds.
Krish NAik: Then let's finalize. Then in that way, I can take up that, because it…
Krish NAik: little bit experiment from my side, because I know that probably for the content preparation, I might need at least 30 days.
Krish NAik: A ball is solo…
Rajat Khanna: interrupt, so do we need to, delete this lambda and S3 bucket, over the billing.
Krish NAik: nothing, nothing. Why will it hit? Lambda… Lambda is purely, like, if you're not hitting it, you won't be getting charged. It's only for the FRL storage that you are using.
Krish NAik: Okay, but if you want to play safe, you can delete it.
Krish NAik: Because ECR, nothing you will be getting charged for anything. S3 also. S3 is, like, very, very cheap, and right now, the amount of document, I think it comes under default only, if you have created a new account.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, and, on the, deployment part, so now, the previous steps it was getting stuck into, those went through, but now it's, on the preparing, build, cache for export, like this.
Krish NAik: Okay, okay. Yeah, like me only, no.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, so…
Krish NAik: Check my screen.
Krish NAik: screen, and then on the way to travel once. Okay, I think it will be my screen only, exporting to GitHub Actions Catcher, because later on, for your next bit, it will be much faster. So I'll be exporting that particular catcher.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright… Yes, Rahul, now I'll tell.
Rahul: Yeah, I'm getting this error of, I don't know, do we have to restart this? Like, it's get failed to resolve.
Krish NAik: Your error is…
Krish NAik: Buildx failed with, failed to build, failed to solve, failed to push. Everything is failed. Does not exist in the registry.
Rahul: Because my name is Serverless, and your name was Server, that's the reason why?
Krish NAik: Yes, it can be, because,
Krish NAik: If your name is, use that correct name, sir, yes, only.
Rajat Khanna: So, error is saying, correct, so the repository name does not exist, so, you need to change the name.
Rahul: Yeah.
Krish NAik: repository name is rad text2SQL hyphen server, it is.
Krish NAik: Written. So, have you checked on your site yet whether it's here or not?
Rahul: No, but, mine was, mine was, this rack.
Krish NAik: If you can raise your hand, I will unmute you.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, you can go ahead.
Krish NAik: Mom.
Sanjay Sagore: Just have a check, I think it is, some issue with respect to the ECR repository.
Sanjay Sagore: Hello, Paul.
Krish NAik: Yes, injected.
Sanjay Sagore: Sorry, so earlier, I was having the issue in committing, but that I had done. Only thing that while deploying, it asking for the environment variable through the Gita.
Sanjay Sagore: I know the manual thing, manual thing I have already done. So, just through the gator.
Sanjay Sagore: I am doing first time.
Sanjay Sagore: So, it asking the environment variable cannot be committed, that .env file. So, do I need to create that particular environment variable in the GitHub secret manager, or how it is?
Krish NAik: Yes, I think, yes, technically, I don't know. You don't need to upload, like.env. One option is manually go, otherwise you can use that, gh, command from the command line. So, automatically, in your repo, those secrets will be added.
Sanjay Sagore: Okay. Or manually, I can create the .env file there only, and then test it, that's it. No, no, manually, where you want to create it.
Sanjay Sagore: In GitHub. Actually, even though, yes, I have committed data…
Krish NAik: No, no, no, no, no, no, don't create… it's a bad practice. Don't do it in GitHub. Use secrets only.
Krish NAik: G8 secret, one is manually, like, go to Settings, then I think under GitHub Action Secrets, there you'll be getting that. Otherwise, you can use, the GitHub command line package, using which GL secret. In that way, also, you can…
Sanjay Sagore: Okay, okay, go.
Krish NAik: Whichever way you feel.
Sanjay Sagore: Okay, okay, thank you.
Krish NAik: Manually do that creation.
Sanjay Sagore: Okay, okay, even though it is not allowing me to do that. Thanks, thanks for calling. One more thing, Paul.
Sanjay Sagore: Saying that, regarding that the multi-agenda, see, really, means our company and other, I can see they are much…
Sanjay Sagore: Buzz, and they're asking you regarding the multiple agent.
Sanjay Sagore: So, are you planning any session or something that we can work on the agents?
Krish NAik: See, I will be talking about agents, but my agents will be much more from the RAG perspective to understand, because my focus is much more towards RAG. I'll be telling you about multiple agents, but just think about one of my main agent will be responsible for chunking, one for embedding in that way. I'll be breaking it.
Krish NAik: And I'll be keeping it in Malton. So, you have to think, because my prospect will be from RAG.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, if you want, like, multiple and other things, because, using Langrap also, I can do it, but, like, like in agents, batches, there, we take multiple use cases. But here, my main focus will be from RAC perspective, much more.
Sanjay Sagore: Okay. Actually.
Krish NAik: But the approach will be same. Okay. It means that the same thing that we teach here also I'll be teaching, but with respect to my projects, it will be different.
Sanjay Sagore: Okay, okay, so there are much… they are asking me the MCP server that… an 8-way protocol, something, I don't know, but, really, okay. Okay, Paul, let's check.
Krish NAik: celebrate.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, meanwhile, if I was doing the build on local, and pushing that same build, so after tagging and pushing the build, do I need to create again that lambda function?
Krish NAik: Nothing.
Krish NAik: you neither… see, if it works as you were testing, in your case also, as it's taking me, I don't know, like, what is the size of this package, Skyro, Pango.
Rajat Khanna: No, no, local, locally, locally, because…
Krish NAik: Local also. Local is not required only while you want to do the build. That is the first thing.
Rajat Khanna: So, I have made that changes now, though, when I am uploading a new document, it is not going into S3 bucket, it is going into local. So, I change the S3 bucket name, and then from the local, I make a build again, tag it again, and push it again.
Krish NAik: Okay, in that way, if you want to do it, like, through the manual approach, then your local build makes sense. But if you don't want to do it, like, directly through CI-CD, then the local approach is not required.
Rajat Khanna: bus point ka pushnatha, ke sumjo meni abi dubara se local build banaya main tag kiya push kiya. Toh dubhara se lambda function banana barte hai.
Krish NAik: lambda function automatically invoke karleta jo bhi image tumara lettail.
Krish NAik: Mmm, mild rate.
Krish NAik: Now, S64 for this is really, really slow.
Krish NAik: Alright, people who want to drop, they can drop, okay?
Krish NAik: as simple.
Krish NAik: Because I think in the next class, then again, this complete thing I will revamp, and I will create automation script, so that rather than going through this step by step, everything is done in one shot. A single bash script that I'll be creating.
Krish NAik: Once my Lambda function gets updated, okay, then I will do the final test with respect to that dock link issue got resolved on.
Krish NAik: Alright, how many are there in participants? Alright.
Krish NAik: Now, does anyone have any question you can ask? Because it looks like…
Rajat Khanna: from Maryland.
Krish NAik: This week, I'll be optimizing this build from 30 minutes to somehow around 15 minutes.
Krish NAik: Likely, 30 minutes is a very, very long time.
Rajat Khanna: Paul, can I share?
Krish NAik: You are already in panelists, no?
Krish NAik: No, no, anybody in panelists can start sharing.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, toh, yehi wa ta'ake amne wo change karana toh ye name change kartia. Kuki, bucket ka name wo secrets mein lag tha, toh yehi variables may be set hai wo, baki chijay.
Krish NAik: Dude.
Rajat Khanna: Yaha, seh fir mane, isko change kartne ke baadanaya build banaya, or build ko tag karke push kartia, istar na se.
Rajat Khanna: Take care.
Krish NAik: This is fine.
Rajat Khanna: EC2 mein, oh, S3 mein.
Krish NAik: S3 may, like, you have to update the Lambda function.
Krish NAik: Okay, like, for that, I think one command will be there, like, AWS LampDate.
Krish NAik: Okay, so once that is updated, then you can.
Rajat Khanna: It will be, like, pulling the latest con.
Rajat Khanna: iligo.
Krish NAik: In case from there also, I think you can do it.
Krish NAik: Because I think I have provided one command. You can check that, new deploy.md, one way, I think one command will look there. Okay, so using that command, you can update your Lambda function.
Rajat Khanna: He did.
Krish NAik: In that same new deploy, the same exact file.
Krish NAik: Alright, so in my case, I think the Lambda deployment is done.
Krish NAik: Okay, so as I can see, it took around 32 minutes, really.
Krish NAik: And with respect to, I think, the initial test and so on, okay? So, let me just go back to my lambda.
Rajat Khanna: either error ayah.
Rajat Khanna: update lambda.
Krish NAik: Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Krish NAik: And I'm checking the first part.
Krish NAik: Canning share? Yes, just wait. While the function is up, I know this docs will be done.
Krish NAik: So, let me see.
Rahul: So, so you are at the stage where update lambda function is completed?
Rahul: Or that?
Krish NAik: is, like, automatically, like, are you asking me?
Rahul: Yes.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, see, my deployment is done, no.
Krish NAik: This one.
Rahul: Okay.
Krish NAik: Okay, the deployment is done, so now I'm just rechecking that the PDF support came or not, that top-in issue got resolved.
Rahul: Correct. So, for example, if I, try to do this right out…
Krish NAik: Choose File. Okay, let's take a different Markdown file. I don't want to use the same one. It should be something small, inception.pdf, I think. Yes, this is fine.
Krish NAik: Insertion.pdf, okay, let me click it automatically, let me see.
Krish NAik: So you said it?
Rahul: 30 minutes, 32 minutes.
Krish NAik: Yes, right now the bill took around 32 minutes.
Krish NAik: But next time I push it, it will be much shorter.
Krish NAik: Because if you don't actually change a lot of things in the image.
Krish NAik: That build is much faster, because everything I am catching
Krish NAik: Okay, so right now, I think Catch 8 is for document processed.
Krish NAik: I think now it is working.
Rahul: Oh…
Krish NAik: Okay.
Rahul: Okay, can I… can I share my screen? I'm… I'm… I don't know, I don't know why I'm stuck at this place.
Krish NAik: Yes, good.
Rahul: So, it still says, I have the same name, Rack, Text to SQL Serverless.
Rahul: repository.
Rahul: And my repository… Oh.
Rahul: This is the name I'm supposed to give?
Krish NAik: Yes, this is your main ECR report from…
Krish NAik: That, like, the Lambda is using.
Krish NAik: Because that is the name of your, I think, function that you showed, which is serverless.
Rahul: Oh!
Krish NAik: Okay, there's, okay, here, yes, yes, here, remove the serverless and keep only SQL.
Rahul: Oh, okay.
Krish NAik: Because that thing is now sorted, I don't think anything, any issues will be there.
Krish NAik: That was only one package which was creating that issue. Now, right now, Angshu,
Krish NAik: After the rise of AI Everyday, we're seeing new and unimaginable agents and automation tools.
Krish NAik: Agents and automation tools will be coming, but, like, behind tools and automation, very less R&D is here. The actual R&D is different.
Krish NAik: It's much more using those things, but actually how to build those things, that is mindful was much more.
Krish NAik: Okay, because things will change, I can say, in the coming months or so. Every week, something comes.
Krish NAik: I think this week, two hot topics. One is that moldabot, ClotBot, if anybody has heard.
Krish NAik: The other one is KimmyK2.5.
Krish NAik: if you guys have, like, followed the news, these two are the major, like, I feel this week, a lot of updates that came.
Rahul: Broadbot, like…
Krish NAik: Yes, Phil?
Rahul: Now, do you have the solution for how to make that more secure? Like.
Rahul: From a security standpoint, I don't…
Krish NAik: You can host it in a private EPS, but again, like,
Krish NAik: The actual source code, I have not looked into a mold port. Okay, rather than I was planning it to host it in a private VPS.
Krish NAik: having two.
Rahul: move.
Krish NAik: Because most of them are, like, in other videos, I saw everybody's purchasing a Mac Mini dedicatedly, but it's not required. EPS is much more cheaper.
Rahul: That's crazy, yeah, that's…
Rajat Khanna: Pull up, screen dekna Egbar.
Krish NAik: Wait. Updating the lambda function… Function not found. Simply, here you have given such a name.
Krish NAik: The lambda function name, that might be wrong, so just check that.
Rajat Khanna: ha.
Krish NAik: Function mein nea nihi banar tao. Meh us function ko sep update karta.
Rajat Khanna: Parhyiph, pipeline se to kabi function benaya ini hamne, yaha, command line se banaatha.
Rajat Khanna: Toad.
Krish NAik: Huh.
Krish NAik: Generally, like, the purpose of updating the function is agar kuch environment variable added hug here. That was the main purpose.
Krish NAik: You can keep the script here also to create a Lambda function. Okay, here also you can do that, but I have not kept it.
Rajat Khanna: Or dousra, jaise ye local hai, dike hai, toh main obo benaya image aur push kari dubara se, or jabye lambda function ka, push kaya thusne ka, already exists. Toh abhi kya.
Rajat Khanna: Commander Baltreathil?
Krish NAik: You use that, you use that command AWS lambda create one.
Krish NAik: To update, I think there will be a different command check, that… and I told you, no, you have to check the document, and the document only is there. Let me check which line number it is.
Krish NAik: AWS, you can do… Testing the function URL.
Krish NAik: function weight, function name. You can use something like this one, AWS lambdaweight function, updated this one.
Rajat Khanna: concern… Don't…
Krish NAik: Okay, so this command, you can use it. The mean was this one. Okay, go to section 8.1 in new underscore deploy.md. From there, you will hit the command.
Krish NAik: When I'm setting the lambda environment variables, then also I'm updating the function. So AWS space lambda space update function.
Krish NAik: You will see that.
Rajat Khanna: jo image ad karni thi woad kari.
Rajat Khanna: jo apne kahata, or yaha pe, tubara main wapis dalty, amainsko pushkan dutantan, ki wo pipeline jo hai but hik se chali.
Krish NAik: Already been do that, no issues when that.
Rahul: Yeah, that's what… yeah, this should work. This is what I'm trying to.
Krish NAik: Okay, so in your case, are you getting any error after that?
Rahul: I just, restarted with the new name, ECR Repository.
Rajat Khanna: Alright, the new name that you have asked, fine.
Krish NAik: A lot of things will be picked up from the catch only.
Rahul: That's why I'm saving the catch in GitHub Actions.
Rahul: I agree with Rajat on the point. See, these are two separate things, so if we… if we wouldn't have created this manually in real time in CICD, we would have done it with deployment, so it should take…
Rahul: Everything from the scratch, so why that repository name exists?
Rajat Khanna: Yes, yes.
Krish NAik: Which repository name exists that you were telling me?
Rahul: Right now, he named… he said, the… the…
Rahul: So, one, we have done it through command prompt, okay? That's…
Krish NAik: Yes, the manual way, yes.
Rahul: Deployment is… should be a… deployment, I can give any XYZ that name, any new name.
Krish NAik: Alright, alright. See, I have not kept that particular logic, because I didn't thought about, again, creating multiple functions. Whenever you are creating multiple functions, again, new function URL will be generated. That part, simply, we can add it. Okay, because the main purpose of updating the lambda was, like, for multiple other environment variables that I can add it.
Krish NAik: I can add that particular logic. It's pretty much that same command, which we have manually added it, I need to add it into the script. That's the only difference. I have not kept it, but yes, we can do that.
Rahul: Okay.
Rahul: And the same project, Paul…
Krish NAik: The main purpose, also, you have to think, if you keep it there, no, every time, new function will be created.
Krish NAik: Because of new function, every time your URL will be changing. My idea was I will keep the URL same.
Krish NAik: I hope you get to my point. Otherwise, if I keep changing the URL, okay, that's a bad practice. That is the major reason why I've not kept creating the Lambda thing.
Rahul: Oh, I see your point, okay.
Rahul: But right, okay.
Rahul: So you can…
Rahul: Yeah, this… okay. So, the Lambda function URL that you have given, the first name is Jebree's name, you know, something which doesn't make sense.
Rahul: So, you can rename it, and you can host one function.
Rahul: That can be used as a common… URL pattern for… accessing your APIs, correct?
Rahul: Like, for example, if I want to name it as multi-rack, text-to-SQL, dot lambda.url.us. Okay.
Krish NAik: Custom domain requirement.
Rahul: Correct, yeah, registered on Route 53, registered, create a certificate, authenticate who has the.
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes.
Rahul: You can only access this thing. How will you do that? In this. You can do that.
Krish NAik: Gross.
Krish NAik: Because I have done it through, API Gateway, actually. I have not done it directly on top of Lambda, because I use… actually, I keep always HTTPI Gateway, but in our case.
Krish NAik: Like, if… because of that 29-second hard limit, I removed that part. Generally, for functions, URL, custom domain, that part, like, I've never done it for Lambda directly, but I know that the thing that you were telling, it is, like, generally the integrations are done with, API gateway.
Krish NAik: Okay,
Rahul: certificates, you know, like, authenticating when… see, if we are trying to run this whole system within a VPC,
Rahul: and, setting up an infrastructure, like, with Plumi or, say, Terraform, why can't I just write a Terraform code for
Rahul: So, the project that you have given, like, the AWS, AWS raginfra.md file, right?
Krish NAik: You can write that entire thing in AWS CloudFormation. Okay, CDK script, you can write it, and the same thing. I think in my last batch, the same thing, I have shown it through CDK only.
Krish NAik: Okay. There I have… yes, through CDK, you can do that, but again, that's the thing, like, everything, if you're working with AWS, even, like, my Python integration with respect to other services also, that can be done.
Krish NAik: CDK is much easier to handle, that I feel, rather than… because there, I think I have used Pulumine.
Rahul: You have used plumbing? You have used plumbing?
Krish NAik: Pulumi is much easier as compared to Terraform. It's much developer-friendly.
Rahul: Thank you.
Krish NAik: Probably for infrastructure, like, it's very, very easy. Pulumi, I feel, much easier as compared to Terraform.
Krish NAik: In Terraform, you need to take care a little bit different, the HashiCorp language.
Krish NAik: the HCL. You need to know a little bit about HCL directly before starting Sterraform. So here, it's pure Python. You'll be writing the entire column in Python.
Krish NAik: So, all those CDK and everything that you'll be doing. So, for developers, it's much friendly, I guess.
Santosh Umargi: Paul, can we look into that, my issue? .
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: Okay, now Lambda function URLs don't support custom domains. You cannot do that. It cannot be integrated with Route 53 or ACM directly.
Krish NAik: Okay, rather than you have to do in the other bit, through… so directly, not possible.
Krish NAik: it out just for you. Yes, so which one now?
Krish NAik: Yes, Antush.
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, and when I upload the file through, no, AWS, it is giving this can't parse JSON, and same I ran in, like, local, no?
Krish NAik: So, yeah, it got.
Santosh Umargi: It worked, like, upload one.
Krish NAik: coming from the catcher hit, actually. This is coming from the catcher hit. Try to show or use that, AWS tail logs. From there, you can actually see the logs.
Santosh Umargi: No, here, first time only, I initialized, no? Gotcha.
Krish NAik: Great.
Santosh Umargi: catch a hit document, huh? On local also, first time I uploaded this document, no?
Santosh Umargi: Yeah, I will show you the cloud.
Krish NAik: No, no, no, so what is the main function?
Krish NAik: It's not working till…
Santosh Umargi: This, this upload one.
Krish NAik: Upload what you have uploaded.
Santosh Umargi: same file, the PDF file uploaded, no? So, can't parse JSON, raw results. So, same code I pushed in the…
Santosh Umargi: Through image, no?
Krish NAik: So, right now, the recent one that I have provided, have you taken that one?
Krish NAik: Or the older one, because recently I've updated the Docker file.
Santosh Umargi: No, no, the recent one, the earlier one only. I not did anything like you did recently, no, in half an hour, right?
Krish NAik: Okay, no, no, no. Actually, like, for PDF, even I was getting the error, then I added 2 or 3 more packages in the Docker file.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay.
Krish NAik: And then again, I redeployed it, and after that, I'm not getting any error.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay. Okay, I will… I mean, so you've added 3 packages, no, that… And push that.
Krish NAik: Okay, now, Rahul, Laspar, your solution, we need a simple routing logic. From your custom domain. In the backend, actually, it will hit the function URL.
Krish NAik: Through routing logic, it will work. And the other option is basically through API Gateway. API Gateway is, complex, at least it uses CloudFront.
Krish NAik: But yes, the way that you were telling, it is possible. Okay, but a workaround has been directly not available in the Lambda function URL, as you can see, but through that, we can do it.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Krish NAik: You don't need to start sharing, because I will stop your sharing.
Krish NAik: So, others can also test our updated the Docker file, so that goppling issue, you guys won't be facing it.
Krish NAik: Okay, Feng Shu is asking from here, the world evolving, how significantly…
Krish NAik: things will change much more, I will say, right? Just wait, because, right now the JPA, VL JPA implementation, it's right now not open source by the Facebook team. Once I feel that it will open source, a lot of things will be impacted.
Krish NAik: Because the JPA paper was also good, or WL JPA…
Krish NAik: We have to look into the computational, like, how much… then a lot of things with respect to parsing, embedding, so a lot of things will change.
Krish NAik: Around. So this year, only just wait for 6 months. And right now, agents are trending, because for automation, it's good. But actually, behind the automation.
Rajat Khanna: What are you?
Krish NAik: this is…
Krish NAik: much framework-based. So, when a lot of frameworks comes into the picture, like, we know that day by day, more than so, so many agentic frameworks that have been launched.
Krish NAik: Very less R&D is there. There's no such R&D. It's actually consuming those core AI stuff and just…
Krish NAik: Creating a product.
Rajat Khanna: CMD di kannat aapko.
Krish NAik: Yeah, sure.
Rajat Khanna: Come on, then go.
Krish NAik: Can you get the latest developments, Aruna is asking? Generally, I track it through, like, alpha signal I2, alphaSignal.ti.
Krish NAik: LinkedIn, Alpha Signal, these are my major ones, I think.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, ye, Command and execute query, AWS function… naihi.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright.
Rajat Khanna: Take care, Filiska, success haggya.
Krish NAik: Alright.
Rajat Khanna: local mein gaya.
Krish NAik: How will we locally make your storage backend?
Krish NAik: Because, there was your storage back at Utai in local configs at Utah tha.
Krish NAik: Because otherwise, there is no other place that I have, kept at. I don't think in my GitHub secrets also that is there, so that it will do an override there.
Krish NAik: I don't think. So check, because it has to be there from…
Rajat Khanna: bucket cache, jo karak dia naata.
Krish NAik: Yes, it's not in GitHub Secrets also.
Krish NAik: So I know that it has to be picked up from config.py.
Krish NAik: Because, there is no other place that I am setting there. Okay, and check that, lambda function, okay? Environments, maybe check up.
Krish NAik: check the Lambda function environment. Generally, like, when I'm updating that particular lambda function, I pass the storage backend is equal to S3, directly there also.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Open your Lambda function, and then you can check it.
Krish NAik: So people, please let me know, the build will take time, even for me, it took around 30 minutes, but after that, Docklin is working fine. I did not get any error from Docklin's side.
Rajat Khanna: Functionable again.
Rajat Khanna: Goodbye.
Krish NAik: region, Dekuna, Europe's talking litava Upan.
Krish NAik: environment variables, like, why I want to click.
Krish NAik: Okay, I see ya.
Krish NAik: Storage backend. Storage backend desk, really, how are you?
Rajat Khanna: Hmm.
Krish NAik: Because I got storage backend S3O.
Krish NAik: the local Khaza era, really. Like, I… Re… don't think.
Krish NAik: And, how you have passed that environment variable through that command only, no? Update lambda function.
Rajat Khanna: Manuel Tokochbini.
Rajat Khanna: commercial bank.
Krish NAik: This is the one here, backend is equal to S3, we've kept it. This is the only, because otherwise there is no scope that picking up that local VRM. I don't think any other place that the definition of local is done in the code also.
Rajat Khanna: Gaga, can't be?
Krish NAik: code page.
Krish NAik: So I think, majorly, tomorrow's side says Sarachi Suho chuka, because local now, you can check, health route may check kalu, health route may be Skritikharay, ya.
Rajat Khanna: wo S3 sehi document jo pada ya, baha sei fetch kar hai, but nahya document jo dalte ha wo local mein store karta hai.
Krish NAik: And in local maklab, generally, local maklab kya, lambda ka local utah. It means that in lambda, I've defined slash temp slash upload.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Kabi bhi asani direct document utar chalay ata, palli local meh jaate local ke baat majata.
Rajat Khanna: Give me a little time later.
Krish NAik: It was right now, even if I checked my design?
Rajat Khanna: Next Saturday koab boulder thing yahi, reframe.
Krish NAik: Because the build is taking 32 minutes. Somehow, some level of optimization latency, 32 minutes.
Rajat Khanna: I, you know, healthy hair.
Rajat Khanna: Response…
Krish NAik: catch a disabled, actual, like, catch a configuration of an ATO with a disabled RR.
Krish NAik: Tiger, which is a disableda.
Rahul: Manually just add those parameters and it will work in the…
Krish NAik: na.
Rajat Khanna: What's up dal diyata.
Rajat Khanna: Manuel libhardiya.
Rajat Khanna: Utu eki repoana, toh bichahi mein isko local se build buna iska, yaha se push kerge dalun banenga tuai.
Krish NAik: And… Always check from that DNB variables directly inside your lambda.
Krish NAik: aerobic.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Last mehatu.
Rajat Khanna: How do you call your Dahlia?
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, toh, first time se pahele ran kiata tabi dal diat.
Krish NAik: Okay. So, there is one…
Rajat Khanna: Shouldn't be seen, man.
Krish NAik: or initialized of Kasenicar power. That's the main thing. Okay, now I feel that…
Krish NAik: Okay, it means that none of your ENV has been initialized, that's why that is telling false, false, false.
Krish NAik: Okay, fine. Lambda function, update karne ke path. Because generally, once you update the lambda function, it takes some time. Within 1 minute, it'll get updated.
Krish NAik: They go, like, you are setting the ENV.
Krish NAik: But, really, it got, there or not.
Krish NAik: That's the thing. Like, application, like, automatically generally takes that.
Krish NAik: Just wait. KK lambda function, wait for the update once.
Krish NAik: Once you have done that, Because of that, because, image we change kyata, na?
Rajat Khanna: Ha, naya image benaya, usko tag kar ke push kara.
Rajat Khanna: AWS update function code, serverless ORA imageURI.
Krish NAik: Alright, because to my environment variable, I've done my update over here.
Krish NAik: Function. So, generally, like, after the function update, only it detects. Tumar is mein false, false keyword. Yahi to mein baat.
Krish NAik: Generally, like, once we have simply done that particular command with respect to the update, it should be showing, but in your case, this is showing false. And even for, as you can see, OPIC is also false, latest is also false.
Rajat Khanna: Dubara seh pist karke tala.
Krish NAik: go cheese.
Rajat Khanna: Huh.
Krish NAik: hack ya.
Rahul: confirm.
Rajat Khanna: Lambda make? Lambda make? Lambda make.
Rahul: File?
Rahul: parameter ad career parodo.
Rajat Khanna: Kutzi?
Rahul: Haha, either she added Kardo.
Rajat Khanna: Check it.
Rahul: API keyit al doho.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Rahul: Conducting options.
Krish NAik: reduce URL.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, it's Komagi…
Krish NAik: Kill, kill.
Rahul: Excuse me.
Krish NAik: Okay, take away.
Krish NAik: Just because of that, it was the issue.
Rajat Khanna: Kunducky.
Rahul: It takes time.
Krish NAik: Double quotes, remove karthah.
Krish NAik: Redis URL hai, usko upper value delete harbenata. Dohar URL iChubar.
Rajat Khanna: leche.
Rahul: I think so.
Krish NAik: OP guide ka.
Rahul: And, Paul, when we are trying to upload through Docker, The email sizes… Increasing by…
Rahul: It is 5.31 GB.
Rahul: Local, it was 5GB, though.
Rahul: Why that huge size of the image?
Krish NAik: local… I think because of these packages that I have added, this Cairo and others, it took around some. Because right now, locally, again, if you try to build, I think it will be similar.
Rahul: And are your local…
Krish NAik: Can't we do that well?
Rahul: Like, can't we only use the packages that were, that is deaf?
Rahul: There are so many packages that we have imported, that's why the…
Rahul: Size, when you look out for the next week, when you're seeing optimization, What are we…
Rahul: Planning to… what are you planning to optimize the image performance, and the build deployment should take lesser time?
Krish NAik: Yes, yes, yes, that's a thing I'll be working on.
Krish NAik: lesser package, because right now, directly, for dependencies of a lot of local TV, dependencies, also, I kept it.
Rahul: Yeah.
Rahul: That's what I was talking about, like, which package is relevant at what level, and why.
Rahul: that understanding needs to be there, right? Because right now, 279 packages, somewhere around 300 packages is what…
Krish NAik: broccoli.
Krish NAik: Dockling is only having more than 60 to 70 packages.
Rahul: Really?
Krish NAik: Yes, directly with all the support, it comes. Okay, because right now, directly I'm installing docklinks. I have not specified that only PDF, so that we can define it in our requirement.txt, that only I need this one. Like, unstructured has that? No, that parameter of all docs.
Krish NAik: Similarly, in docked links, also, you can do that particular optimization that only for PDF, only, like, based on the file formats. So, by… in that way, you can actually reduce the number of requirements.
Rahul: Got it.
Rajat Khanna: wo sahihi banenga.
Rajat Khanna: To usko kasi tikk karoge.
Rajat Khanna: usme woh jo a SQL query hai, wohikkar ke benata ki harbahar.
Rajat Khanna: Joki query toh LLM generate karta aur LLM.
Krish NAik: masal evaluate karna.
Rajat Khanna: Booster…
Krish NAik: side of.
Krish NAik: You… Bugustan…
Rajat Khanna: Ugh.
Rajat Khanna: The booster is a context or weightage load dedicated to LLM generated SQL to push model towards the right table and column join.
Krish NAik: Okay, Tika. Towards the right, Devin Tika.
Krish NAik: schema retrieval mein kar dia, toh schema palli mein beij detang, booster is applied in between. Thi ito prong te level mein page rah.
Rajat Khanna: ush nangga booster.
Krish NAik: booster toher ad naikum.
Krish NAik: Rather than evaluation through multiple examples through EHE booster, would you be taking?
Rajat Khanna: confidence, hi lagra.
Krish NAik: The more error you get, the more confidence you have.
Rajat Khanna: project dingh.
Krish NAik: Right now, the job market is very unstable.
Rahul: develop super… Paul, I would say that with the change, and that's my personal view.
Rahul: Whatever you think, like, develop product of your own, and keep working on that product. Any… anything that you have experience with.
Rajat Khanna: Hmm, hmm.
Rahul: like, the UCIQ, modify, or identify.
Rahul: And then… you will get strong on that point.
Rajat Khanna: current project mein, meherko koi alignment nahi. Tohagar wo, maybe shya bench pay mu kar den gya mujah nahi idea ke bench pay nahya project melee nahi melee.
Rajat Khanna: Toh mein dubar majase front-end developer room. Toh tu bara front end mein change karne kejay mais, whatcharatha ke agar change karong ga hi toher isai mein change kar lunga janne hai mein change kar lunga.
Rajat Khanna: Toh, aviv mereko hare ke bay confidence bhi hai wo change karnega kini.
Rahul: And that's what Paul is trying to say, and… see… just… develop… one…
Rahul: product. Yes, I may Google, DeepMind may project,
Rahul: Proposal dalata. Unone $10,000 ka credit DDI. Approve karke.
Rahul: Kuchny tha, ek idea jisko apne notebook LLM pe dala, aur uska video banak wipe coding karke dal dia, ki ye mere domain mein yeh mere expertise hai, mein essa sushaun, asa kart.
Rahul: What we're trying to say is throw up your idea right now on any platform and…
Rahul: submit to every competition that is available right now. Just…
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Rahul: keep, like, kuch bhi constitu setum UI ke bande ho, right?
Rajat Khanna: Hmm, you know.
Rahul: Hawaii.
Rahul: uska troubleshooting kuch panna saktur ragpe.
Rahul: Chatbox, yeah, yeah.
Rajat Khanna: wo ban aluna wahi wo jo pole karinage kaam kartne se confidence hatha hai.
Rajat Khanna: To meir ko hai ke bhi project agar current company walnay nahi diasundho jet nahi AP yang kuch bhai. Toh agar mein bahar change karke chalajata moke interview clear oka aapcha leghe company mein. Toh baha, toh shuru mein toh dare atani ya, jud boh hai.
Krish NAik: They go, simple bhate agar puch name Milra, no, start open source something. GitHub Belu, kudka package bana, so that it becomes easier for any developers to do that particular integration in their current workflow. Aur agar tumara project mein simple, pachas or starvi ayata, na, it's a big deal.
Krish NAik: It can be something like a utility, okay, but it's actually helpful. So, vasekarke, like, you can do, like, major in the market, Llama Index, land chain, and from Sapka, SA chi sa Jiska with a proper library bin name ana.
Krish NAik: directly model to take, like, you can look into that part, and then you can export. Even for Achikar as a metadata monarchy, we go directly within AI.
Rajat Khanna: Awesome.
Krish NAik: you can think about a particular thing, and you.
Rajat Khanna: Toh agar chance millay change karke rag janne I pem karne ka, toh, I should take that chance may ya pushna jar toh.
Rajat Khanna: dikatariya.
Rajat Khanna: Good enough.
Krish NAik: So, first of all, to get that particular chance, it means that tumja bhatar wah project moi lingiya nih.
Rajat Khanna: To scale me to showcase, because you are coming from an entirely different track.
Krish NAik: maths-related hota. Tota entry easy hota. Jab, completely, you are changing a different stack. Agar complete jaise tum full stack value hota. It means that.
Krish NAik: You know, like, Node.js, backend for Zada Kant KU. It becomes much easier.
Krish NAik: I say, Java developer po mehai kar sakta. Muja bata, like, easily Python karuchi kam kar saktah. Only the things that I need to teach him is with respect to certain concepts with respect to LL.
Krish NAik: So, back in English and again…
Rajat Khanna: Back-end API development, node express karke but to athi, ushmein, tohoi, challenge mein ha.
Krish NAik: matter karta hai.
Rajat Khanna: Karzagtugini.
Krish NAik: Simply, most of the things we are doing it in Python. Later on, if somebody asks you to switch it to Rust and others.
Krish NAik: That adaptability as a programmer is important.
Rahul: Paul, yeah, I'm facing this, issue now. Finally, it got… configuration verification failed, you know?
Rahul: So…
Krish NAik: Configuration verification, share your screen, because I need to look into that one.
Rahul: Yeah.
Krish NAik: Just wait.
Rajat Khanna: In your case, again, rebuild, I'm looking into Rao screen, Raul, first of all, show me.
Krish NAik: What is the one error that you were getting?
Krish NAik: User… okay, this is serverless, this is fine, fine, fine. These are the environment variables update. Updating the Lambda environment variables.
Rahul: So vaginary.
Rahul: So, test deployment… is failing.
Rahul: It says health, endpoint.
Rahul: Max retry attempts.
Krish NAik: Okay, take care. So, generally, I may help check through example, test file upload karke. Generally, I check it.
Krish NAik: So, deployment test passed. I know your Lambda function URL is working. Now, after the poll start, you can, look into the logs from, CloudWatch directly of your Lambda. Check that.
Krish NAik: Okay, alright. Access denied to S3 bucket.
Krish NAik: Falling back to local.
Krish NAik: Check this one.
Krish NAik: S3 bucket issue is there something.
Rahul: Why, my love… what did I make change? Like… So, in the deployment…
Krish NAik: Actually, this gets… picked up from the guitar, GitHub sequence.
Rahul: Oh, GitHub, okay… GitHub secrets, man. I have put the S3 as.
Krish NAik: There is 3 catch up with him.
Krish NAik: The splash.
Rahul: So, T-Smith, I just put the same bucket name which is there in the… In the S3.
Krish NAik: Previous to this, check the environment variable in the current lambda.
Krish NAik: I think there, also, you have that environment, because right now, this environment file doesn't matter.
Rahul: I have kept the same name.
Krish NAik: Okay, check, equal lambda, my checker, I think, because if it is same, then it should… be walking.
Rahul: Lambda…
Krish NAik: Lambda environment variables mean factor.
Rahul: Okay, okay, okay.
Rahul: S3S3 is also the same name.
Krish NAik: Because…
Krish NAik: If this is there, it's simple that I can say, versus this is there, then how it can say that it's failing? Okay, now in your AWS CloudWatch logs.
Krish NAik: Go back.
Rahul: Oh, here it says, different name in conflict.
Krish NAik: Okay, that's why this thing I told you.
Rahul: Oh.
Rahul: That's why, in the app.config.
Krish NAik: Yes, I think because of this, Mundi.
Krish NAik: During the upload.
Rajat Khanna: Paul Sara complete honigawa ye test deployment mein failure aya GitHub mein.
Krish NAik: test deployment mechan, generally, I check the routes, that the routes are working or not. In your case, which route is telling that, failed with the logic, returns, okay, it could not. Check the lambda function status.
Krish NAik: Verify the APHLT API gateway, the check the CloudWatch logs quickly. CloudWatch log sealji bata challenge.
Krish NAik: You can do that, or you can use AWS.
Krish NAik: tail logs.commd also is fine.
Rajat Khanna: Local medalukkahluog.
Krish NAik: any AWS Cloud Watch job Lambda Function code loop.
Rajat Khanna: Hmm.
Krish NAik: O lambda function jo specific tomorrow lambda, wokan.
Krish NAik: No, the ER page job, monitor, monitor.
Krish NAik: Monitor me jagnya, view club watch logs like kaya na, beach me.
Krish NAik: Opera.
Krish NAik: Up Parja Udikra, top me, view CloudWatch Logs. Right-hand side, view CloudWatch Logs.
Krish NAik: Alawando.
Rajat Khanna: Initializing token. Access denied S3 bucket.
Rajat Khanna: Falling back to local.
Rajat Khanna: mein.
Rajat Khanna: Documented.
Krish NAik: Lambda ke saath estrika kal class mein many dihant haik policy. Yeske karen buh tumara woh tayadan mo nahi karoge, toh generally ya tak yeh thick, tumara upaise jaweigbar.
Krish NAik: Orko error hackya, if cello local mein safekar, other errors, check for that. Invalid header ka kuchara, local ignit.
Krish NAik: Exception, failed to connect to Pinecone Index.
Krish NAik: kibbar.
Krish NAik: other GitHub secrets may… other…
Krish NAik: If you're keeping something blank, also, no. During the deployment, blank BI jata, it becomes a problem.
Krish NAik: GitHub Secrets over.
Krish NAik: kitap secret saupload kar.
Krish NAik: And even check even in your Lambda also, that part.
Rajat Khanna: Pinecone… Index name… Pinecone API key.
Krish NAik: mein nahara.
Krish NAik: kayu.
Krish NAik: Trust policy karjek file diat.
Rajat Khanna: Actions… Pinecone.
Krish NAik: GitHub Secrets, or donu jagap update cardin.
Rajat Khanna: Hello, yaha. Pinecone API key.
Krish NAik: Huh.
Rajat Khanna: Environment.
Rajat Khanna: And it'll update…
Krish NAik: Autumn… lambda 2S3 kilni, buwala, add gardo. I think yesterday it had add S3 permissions, step 4.
Rajat Khanna: Pretty… But local meinh, we get seini chalra, but local mehe ja.
Krish NAik: Local mein subchal ja ta hai.
Krish NAik: That's the main thing.
Rajat Khanna: Okay, a B,
Rajat Khanna: Good review of me.
Rajat Khanna: Najo.
Krish NAik: Nietzsche, Nietzsche, Nietzsche, Nietzsche.
Krish NAik: Lambda S3 policy.
Krish NAik: Attach na jyo tumara Wukarna padi yan.
Rajat Khanna: M lambda needs to read right as 3 in the document, Yvala.
Krish NAik: No.
Rajat Khanna: kartina, which…
Krish NAik: is commander.
Krish NAik: or commande.
Rajat Khanna: Can… Yearly. Create and retouch policy.
Krish NAik: Yeah.
Rajat Khanna: Yemeni kar di kalu.
Rajat Khanna: Error.
Rajat Khanna: And when calling.
Krish NAik: Okay, entity already exists, Matlavi Par Choke Hotung.
Rajat Khanna: Huh.
Krish NAik: niche jo habi agbar execut kar do. I think it's second may be good chat, JWS account ID ka to.
Krish NAik: your permission has, then, like, YS3 is getting rejected.
Krish NAik: Okay, done, Igbar. Uske wa lambda jo function ke bada wala command tha, directly paste it here.
Rajat Khanna: Yovala?
Krish NAik: karmun.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: Last column mein kama, last meh thori na kuma chali.
Krish NAik: Oh.
Rajat Khanna: Let's…
Krish NAik: Bus, or kuchmun.
Krish NAik: Wait for a lambda function update only my time left, 60 seconds.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Krish NAik: usi function.
Krish NAik: But dihantu karcha yam.
Rajat Khanna: Lambda mein o manually add kyata na bhi.
Krish NAik: update kartiya.
Krish NAik: Tomorrow.
Krish NAik: kaya.
Krish NAik: It could be a ticket.
Krish NAik: This part is done, iske baat tum function URL webh check karna.
Rajat Khanna: Yoval.
Krish NAik: Check this one.
Rajat Khanna: Yan na…
Krish NAik: Are we manually many updates here, na?
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Rajat Khanna: But that's right.
Rajat Khanna: opik to register.
Krish NAik: EYME tomorrow.
Krish NAik: Upload to me.
Krish NAik: local mejorai ki permission denied RA.
Krish NAik: Tomorrow, Lambda 2Shima.
Rajat Khanna: Okay.
Rajat Khanna: Normally, companies pipeline, jahan peer agana fail. Toho move hi nahi karta hai. Last mein routes check kari ho.
Rajat Khanna: Tos me voistaran selectengo cuco vi fe luegoado muy nigga.
Krish NAik: Meera, deployment meini, where jo deployment ke ba, jo routcept me testing.
Rajat Khanna: And they go locally ga.
Krish NAik: AWS my job. Permission issue, man.
Krish NAik: I'm users related to Tumara permission issuer.
Krish NAik: Because when I execute this one, just wait.
Krish NAik: Double turn, just wait here when I do that.
Krish NAik: policy…
Rajat Khanna: You don't do as okay?
Rajat Khanna: Manual Policy.
Krish NAik: Nay, Manuel Vesal.
Krish NAik: Thanks, scare me alone, and get account ID.
Krish NAik: If your deployment policy is not… So much… required… Attach. S3 bucket image, okay?
Krish NAik: S3 life cycle, okay, TK, particularly.
Krish NAik: Because it is tomorrow, S3, which permission-related, huh?
Krish NAik: You speak of full access ana na, I am in government.
Krish NAik: Full access is there, I don't think any other important things that needs to be configured.
Krish NAik: Mmm, good.
Rahul: Yeah, ECS container full access is required, right?
Krish NAik: E-C-R, not E-C-S.
Rahul: Yeah, ECR, so ECL.
Rahul: I…
Rajat Khanna: Kai Policy Kanam.
Rajat Khanna: Yeah, pinata.
Krish NAik: Because Cloud Virtual allows Maja, again, if it's healing.
Rajat Khanna: Kidogenic?
Krish NAik: Nico.
Rajat Khanna: glow.
Rajat Khanna: Oh, yeah.
Krish NAik: Okay, many retried access, don't know the account.
Rajat Khanna: Yahampi koi OX.
Krish NAik: Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Krish NAik: munga.
Rajat Khanna: Tumara bakit ka nim ka.
Rajat Khanna: War architecture.
Krish NAik: name.
Rajat Khanna: Rajat123K.
Krish NAik: Rajat jo 123 ethodina facade, to meera policy qualify, jo policy to me lagai uskein niche resource ERN liha hota hai, usme specific jo bakit kan name hota, ja se meene rag karke diata, rag star kar dinaya, ye tumara jo… naming convention ke baja seura ye nam dukapi guru.
Rajat Khanna: Hanji. Guardia.
Krish NAik: same step. Already exists.
Rajat Khanna: be there?
Krish NAik: est-ce que upperwala command?
Krish NAik: Happara quitavo.
Krish NAik: Alpero key.
Rajat Khanna: I am.
Krish NAik: Aparuki aurekbar?
Krish NAik: Okay, ye jo, I am create policy. Uske baat ye temp file image aake johara ye lambda S3…
Krish NAik: Okay.
Rajat Khanna: It's streaming.
Krish NAik: Upar wala jo katawala commandewala command me jaw.
Krish NAik: rag hyphen kache hyphen star. Kam nahi kari.
Rajat Khanna: Chao.
Krish NAik: aptunko ja.
Rajat Khanna: haig.
Krish NAik: generally, I keep at least 8 to, characters that I keep.
Krish NAik: That you can test if you wanted.
Krish NAik: You see, like…
Rajat Khanna: my…
Krish NAik: any name.
Krish NAik: Always, like, in the code, put change order that you need to actually look.
Rajat Khanna: Okay. Essentially.
Rajat Khanna: Mike and Tilig dito.
Krish NAik: My karke.
Krish NAik: Just every year. I think this file will be getting updated.
Rajat Khanna: Okay… Tempoali… Tempovali ke baat.
Krish NAik: Do those updates.
Krish NAik: Okay.
Krish NAik: Won't need to say anything.
Rahul: Oh, Paul, it's 12 here, so I'm…
Krish NAik: Alright, fine, you can drop. Okay. Yeah. Because you can check the bill to go to sleep, and then later on, check that.
Krish NAik: Correct, okay. And then you can inform me. Because I hope…
Rahul: How much time will it take? I'm… I'm going to convert this project into a complete AWS rag infra.md, you know?
Rahul: And… Can I… yeah, I'm just trying to use this project, as a use case, and…
Rahul: convert the existing code infrastructure into a Plumi file, and put all the AWS-related RAG infrastructure, because I think this project could be of use for me, you know.
Krish NAik: it, you can do that, there is no issue. See, generally, just wait, so next week, what I will do, probably, rather than keyword working, the same thing, okay, it's better to create a group, okay, and I will tell someone, because I think in your batch.
Krish NAik: best specialized guys, Motazam only, I will ask him, okay, that at least a few things with respect to certain things. He's very good in Terraform, I know. Okay, so, but, again, like.
Rahul: Yeah.
Krish NAik: Yaga, it's not about adding anyone, only core people, the things that they can, only those, they are willing to add.
Krish NAik: So, fine, because that RAG Inferi already have. So, if you take this particular context, okay, and you want to do that with AWS CDK? No, no, that part is fine. You can do that, because, again, that entire infra, you can launch it in one shot.
Rahul: Yeah, I haven't played with Plumi, I'm good at Terraform, so I'm just thinking…
Krish NAik: Okay, fine, then do it in Terraform. Because for initial, whenever you were working with infrastructure provisioning, I said, start with Pulubi, then move to Terraform. If you're good with Terraform, then directly you can start with Terraform.
Rahul: Yeah, yeah. No, I'm… I haven't played with Plumi, so I… what… that's what I was thinking, to play with Plumi as a…
Rahul: as a project, to convert… take a Plumi script.
Krish NAik: Actually, that script will be in Python only.
Rahul: Yeah, yeah, in Python only, that's what I just…
Krish NAik: That's futile.
Krish NAik: Yes, you can take that out, yes.
Rahul: Okay.
Rahul: And I'll share you the repo for review, you know, like, if you can…
Krish NAik: elevate twin.
Rahul: And if you can… if you have someone that you can pair me up.
Krish NAik: Create a GitHub, open one, okay, and then, like, keep it as a project. Like, every… in GitHub River, you can create a project in simple blocks, so that, like, later on, if anybody wants to look into that, even for you, it'll be much easier to maintain it.
Krish NAik: Just, what we call it, just like Trello.
Rahul: Prello, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
Rahul: Sounds good, thanks. Thanks, Paul.
Krish NAik: Alright, check it? Okay, I think it should work. Okay, any other questions you want to ask, guys, you can ask, okay. Otherwise, like, next.
Krish NAik: Saturday, we'll be doing that, particular discussion.
Santosh Umargi: Paul, in deploy.yaml, no, useDoclink, is there, no? So there, also, we have to set it as a true.
Krish NAik: Yes.
Krish NAik: Actually, like, even there you can… later on, actually, I updated, no, manually. So there, I kept that particular variable as true. Otherwise, you can change there also as true.
Santosh Umargi: Okay, okay. Because I, my deployment is succeeded, and, I tested, no? So that error is giving, yeah.
Krish NAik: Regarding Dr. Oak.
Krish NAik: Alright, fine then, guys, okay, so for today, then I'll be concluding the session. Next week, again, this complete thing I will try to automate, and I will try to optimize a few things on Docker level, at least because the build is taking 30 minutes, so let's see, like, how I can do that.
Krish NAik: But in the source code, I won't be doing any changes. It's only doing me in the DockerLib. If it is at least 2 minutes, 3 minutes, how much I can reduce, I will check that back. Okay, so next Saturday also, the same discussion, and then probably on Sunday, we'll be starting with the project 3 of Hybrid.
Krish NAik: Will it help if I join other training batches? Now, Rasse, you have to just be good on that particular fundamentals part. If you feel that you've been working with Jennai for 2-3 years, then it becomes much easier. If you are not then directly adapting, it becomes much harder, I feel.
Krish NAik: Alright guys, hub everyone, thanks for joining.